<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_PTBR_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_CUTSCENES">

        <LanguageRef>LANG_PTBR</LanguageRef>

        <Contributors>
            <Name>Oxymoron Games</Name>
        </Contributors>

        <LocalizedStrings>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_SUBHEADING_1</LocID>                  <Text>United Nations of Solar System - Chapter 1</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_SUBHEADING_2</LocID>                  <Text>United Nations of Solar System - Chapter 2</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_SUBHEADING_3</LocID>                  <Text>United Nations of Solar System - Chapter 3</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_SUBHEADING_4</LocID>                  <Text>United Nations of Solar System - Chapter 4</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_HEADING_1</LocID>                     <Text>The Escape Module</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_TEXT_1</LocID>                        <Text>It has been several months since a terrorist attack deprived the Siren System of its only means of interstellar travel. \n\nThe Gate Station, a unique creation of the ancient Primals that guided energy streams used by spaceships, suffered tremendous damage and the Ranock - the strongest ship in the UNSS fleet, entrusted with its protection, was completely destroyed.\n\n Only one escape module made a landing, but ended up in Fossorian territory. Their Supreme Leader refused any investigation, but Furret's rebellion changed the tides. \n\nCaptain Arjun Rao joins a team of Hesperidian investigators to represent humans in the ongoing search. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_LVL1_THE_END</LocID>                   <Text>Without the support of the Solar System, the UNSS is losing ground. Colony after colony is gaining independence, but the situation may be reversed yet.\n\nNow, after several months, our investigators finally have a strong lead. Has interstellar travel been lost for good? Are the Fossorians solemnly responsible for the attack? The survivor from the escape module may hold the answers. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>



            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_HEADING_2</LocID>                     <Text>Labour Camp</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_TEXT_2</LocID>                        <Text>Our investigators decided to rescue Navigator Maya - the only survivor from the crashed escape module.\n\nHer current whereabouts (if you believe the word of a Fossorian) are near the Free Site colony located at the edge of the Sovereighn Fleet territory.\n\n Arranging her escape from the labor camp won't be easy, but new information about the Gate Station attack may reopen the path to the Solar System once more.\n\nLet's hope she is not in another castle.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_LVL2_THE_END</LocID>                   <Text>The Hesperidian traitor John Smith 7A must answer for his crimes. But what made him arrange the attack that has cut the UNSS from the Solar System?\n\nRisking his career and life, Captain Rao decides to pursue Smith to the landing site of the Gate Station's core.\n\n With a little bit of luck, he will catch the traitor before he further damages the core and disables space travel for good. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_HEADING_3</LocID>                     <Text>The Core</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_TEXT_3</LocID>                        <Text>While the interrogation of Demon Ragna - a confederate of traitor John Smith 7A- continues, Captain Rao arrives at the area where the core of The Gate Station landed.\n\nHe managed to avoid all UNSS checkpoints along the way as the rigid UNSS rules are playing against him at this moment. But as he reaches his destination he can no longer avoid confrontation with UNSS forces loyal to the traitorous commander. \n\nDoctor Brown and Navigator Maya promised to join Captain Rao as soon as they finished the interrogation and officially exposed the traitor. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_LVL3_THE_END</LocID>                   <Text>All the effort turned in vain after the first look at the devastated core of the Gate Station. Captain Raon paid the most.\n\nHis UNSS contract has been revoked and he is no longer a part of the organization that gave him not only a home but a purpose.\n\nIt may appear as the end but men like Captain Rao hardly admit the defeat even when everything seems lost.    </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_HEADING_4</LocID>                     <Text>Paved with Good Intentions</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_TEXT_4</LocID>                        <Text>Several months after the information that The Gate Station will never be repaired leaked, the UNSS witnessed a mass exodus of its citizens. Many colonies simply lost interest in paying taxes to a dying faction.\n\nIn the time of deepest crisis, a message came to the hands of special investigators, Doctor Brown and Lieutenant Maya. The sender is no one else than the long-time missing Ex-captain Rao, who went to a self-imposed exile after his rather "unceremonious" departure from the UNSS. \n\nThe message is very cryptic, but hints that he may have discovered a way how to reverse the crisis and turn the tide in the favor of the UNSS once more.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_LVL4_THE_END</LocID>                   <Text>The events surrounding the demise of "the traitor" John Smith 7A are highly classified. But, soon after, the repaired Gate Station welcomed several minor transports from the Solar System.\n\n It was not much, but enough for the UNSS to regain not only the trust of its citizens, but also remind the other factions of the might of the Solar System standing behind the UNSS.\n\nThe conspiracy theorists claim that a new shadow figure is leading the steps of the UNSS, but you should now know better than to trust any old gossip. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_1_OBJECTIVE_1</LocID>                 <Text>Find the escape module</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

        </LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
