<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_KO_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_CUTSCENES">

        <LanguageRef>LANG_KO</LanguageRef>

        <Contributors>
            <Name>Oxymoron Games</Name>
        </Contributors>

        <LocalizedStrings>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_SUBHEADING_1</LocID>                  <Text>United Nations of the Solar System - Chapter 1</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_SUBHEADING_2</LocID>                  <Text>United Nations of the Solar System - Chapter 2</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_SUBHEADING_3</LocID>                  <Text>United Nations of the Solar System - Chapter 3</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_SUBHEADING_4</LocID>                  <Text>United Nations of the Solar System - Chapter 4</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_HEADING_1</LocID>                     <Text>The Escape Module</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_TEXT_1</LocID>                        <Text>It has been several months since a terrorist attack deprived the Siren System of its only means of interstellar travel - The Gate Station. \n\n The Gate, a unique relic of the ancient Primals, suffered tremendous damage, and the Ranock - the flagship of the UNSS fleet charged with protecting the ancient lifeline completely destroyed.\n\n Only one of its escape modules survived the attack, and it landed in Fossorian territory. The Fossorian Supreme Leader initially refused any investigation attempts, but Furret's rebellion changed that. \n\nCaptain Arjun Rao teams up with Hesperidian investigators as the token human to search for the missing module.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_LVL1_THE_END</LocID>                   <Text>Without the support of the Solar System, the UNSS is losing ground. Colony after colony is gaining independence, but the situation may yet be reversed.\n\nAfter several months of dead ends, our investigators finally have a strong lead. Has interstellar travel been lost for good? Are the Fossorians solely responsible for the attack? The escape module's survivor may hold the answers.  </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>



            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_HEADING_2</LocID>                     <Text>Labour Camp</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_TEXT_2</LocID>                        <Text>Our investigators have decided to attempt to rescue Navigator Maya - the only survivor from the crashed escape module.\n\nHer current whereabouts (if you believe the word of a Fossorian) is near the Freeside colony located at the edge of Sovereign Fleet territory.\n\n Helping her escape from the labor camp there won't be easy, but new information about the Gate Station attack may reopen the path to the Solar System once more.\n\n Let's hope the intelligence is correct, and she's not somewhere else.  </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_LVL2_THE_END</LocID>                   <Text>The Hesperidian traitor John Smith 7A must answer for his crimes. But what made him arrange the attack that cut the UNSS from the Solar System?\n\nRisking his career and life, Captain Rao decides to pursue Smith to the landing site of the Gate Station's core.\n\n With a little luck, the captain will catch the traitor before he further damages the core and halts interstellar travel for good. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_HEADING_3</LocID>                     <Text>The Core</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_TEXT_3</LocID>                        <Text>While Demon Ragna, a confederate of the traitor John Smith 7A, is being interrogated, Captain Rao heads to the suspected landing site of the Gate Station Core.\n\n Until he can get on the other side of the UNSS's rigid regulations, he must stay clear of their checkpoints. As he approaches his goal, his luck runs out, and he can no longer avoid confrontation with the UNSS forces loyal to the traitorous commander. \n\nDoctor Brown and Navigator Maya have promised to join Captain Rao as soon as they complete their interrogation and officially expose the traitor. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_LVL3_THE_END</LocID>                   <Text>All efforts appear in vain once they get their first look at the devastated Gate Station core. Captain Rao pays the highest price.\n\nHis UNSS contract is revoked, and he is no longer a part of the organization that gave him both a home and a purpose.\n\nIt appears to be the end for Captain Rao, but he's hardly a man to admit defeat, even when it's staring him right in the face.    </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_HEADING_4</LocID>                     <Text>Paved with Good Intentions</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_TEXT_4</LocID>                        <Text>Several months after the intel that the Gate Station would never be repaired leaked, the UNSS witnessed a mass exodus of its citizens. Many colonies simply lost interest in paying taxes to a dying faction. \n\n When the crisis was at its deepest, a message fell into the laps of special investigators, Doctor Brown and Lieutenant Maya. The sender was none other than the long-lost Ex-captain Rao, who went to a self-imposed exile after his rather "unceremonious" departure from the UNSS. \n\n His message is very cryptic but hints that he may have discovered a way to reverse the crisis and turn the tide in favor of the UNSS once more.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_LVL4_THE_END</LocID>                   <Text>The events surrounding the demise of "the traitor" John Smith 7A are highly classified. But soon after his fall, several transports from the Solar System passed through the newly repaired Gate Station. .\n\n It was hardly a fleet, but it was enough for the UNSS to regain both the trust of its citizens and remind the other factions in the system that the might of the Solar System once again supported the local UNSS presence. \n\nConspiracy theorists claim that a new shadowy figure now consults the UNSS, but you should now know better than to trust idle gossip. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_EMPIRE_1_OBJECTIVE_1</LocID>                 <Text>Find the Escape Module</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

        </LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
