<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_RU_CAMPAIGN_PIRATES_CUTSCENES">

        <LanguageRef>LANG_RU</LanguageRef>

        <Contributors>
            <Name>Oxymoron Games</Name>
        </Contributors>

        <LocalizedStrings>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_PIRATES_SUBHEADING_1</LocID>                  <Text>Sovereign Fleet - Chapter 1</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_PIRATES_SUBHEADING_2</LocID>                  <Text>Sovereign Fleet - Chapter 2</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_PIRATES_SUBHEADING_3</LocID>                  <Text>Sovereign Fleet - Chapter 3</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_PIRATES_SUBHEADING_4</LocID>                  <Text>Sovereign Fleet - Chapter 4</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_PIRATES_HEADING_1</LocID>                     <Text>Two make company</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_PIRATES_TEXT_1</LocID>                        <Text>Fossorian marauders invading the Sovereign colonies is a common affair, but this time it's massive! Enemy forces are numerous and well coordinated. Maybe too well. The UNSS military advisors might be an explanation for that unusual level of precision.\n\nA Sovereign colony under the protection of Gran Manny is one of those facing the attack. The Fossorians seem to have destroyed the radio towers around it, because nobody answered Manny's calls for help.\n\nBy a stroke of luck, the Sovereign Fleet's captain, Annika, hero of the battle for Kelvin Station, was near when the attack began. \n\nHer timely arrival could turn the tide of battle. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CAMPAIGN_PIRATES_LVL1_THE_END</LocID>                   <Text>As Annika watched the Hesperidian dragging Gran Manny off, her mind was occupied only by one thought: the plan, though cruel, is bearing fruit. \n\nThe Hesperidian will lead the Sovereigns to the people who are behind the attacks, and the current direction of his ship suggests that Chimera, the third and least charted planet of the Siren System, is the destination.  </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>



            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_PIRATES_HEADING_2</LocID>                     <Text>The Hunt</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_PIRATES_TEXT_2</LocID>                        <Text>Annika and Tin traveled deep into the jungles of planet Chimera.\n\nThey are looking for Annika's Sovereign friends, Doug Porter and #925.\n\nThe Sovereigns tracked the Hesperidian commander responsible for the kidnapping of Gran Manny, to a secret UNSS facility. Doug and #925 are scouting ahead, waiting to be joined by Annika. \n\nOnce they meet, they will attack the facility and put an end to the unprovoked attacks on Sovereign's colonies and mysterious disappearances of the Sovereign Fleet's captains.  </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CAMPAIGN_PIRATES_LVL2_THE_END</LocID>                   <Text>Although the engine flames swallowed the mysterious enemy whole, it emerged unharmed. The UNSS must have made a pact with this devil in order to hunt down all the Sovereign Fleet's captains. \n\nBut what is that Thing, why does it look for the cores, and what are the limits of its powers? Some answers may be sealed inside Tin's memory. Perhaps some of them could be accessed. The only man who can be trusted with such a task is Professor Zane.  </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>


            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_PIRATES_HEADING_3</LocID>                     <Text>Strange Research</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_PIRATES_TEXT_3</LocID>                        <Text>After a short while, Chiquita landed at the last known location that the eccentric, but brilliant scientist, Professor Zane, visited. \n\nThese territories belong to the Tumori tribes, parasitic aliens, and Siren System natives known for hijacking local fauna to serve as their hosts. \n\nThe evidence convicting Annika of being an UNSS spy probably reached the Sovereigns by now; therefore, she expects less than a warm welcome from the nearby colony. Hopefully, Zane will see the bigger picture and help access the Tins' memory. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CAMPAIGN_PIRATES_LVL3_THE_END</LocID>                   <Text>Tin's memory hides no more secrets. The False Mother is hunting the Sovereign captains to learn about the whereabouts of the cores. Many of them still contain the only things powerful enough to threaten her - the other clones of the Allmother, a long dead goddess of the Children of the Source. \n\nThe safest way to prevent being challenged is if she destroys all the immature clones while they are still harmless. \n\nArmed by that knowledge, Tin and Annika must act swiftly to disrupt the plans of the False Mother and save a possible challenger! </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>


            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_PIRATES_HEADING_4</LocID>                     <Text>The Hero of Kelvin</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_PIRATES_TEXT_4</LocID>                        <Text>Trying to avoid the UNSS's attention often brought Annika to the strangest of places. Therefore, she was able to lead Tin to one of the cores hidden in a border region of planet Scylla. \n\nBy now, the False Mother must have finished the interrogation of her Sovereign captives, and learned the whereabouts of all remaining cores scattered around the system. But, with a little bit of luck, she will be occupied raiding a different one.  </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CAMPAIGN_PIRATES_LVL4_THE_END</LocID>                   <Text>Sometimes it's not about defeating the darkness, but about holding it in a little longer. Annika's final sacrifice gave Tin enough time to escape on board of Chiquita. \n\nThe little being, sleeping in his arms, is the only hope for defeating the rising empire of the False Mother. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

        </LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
