<Database>
  <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_RU_DEMO_MAP_NEXT_FEST">
    <LanguageRef>LANG_RU</LanguageRef>
    <Contributors>
      <Name>AlexSnowLeo</Name>
    </Contributors>
    <LocalizedStrings>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST</LocID>
        <Text>ДЕМО</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_INTRODUCTION</LocID>
        <Text>Полковник Снифф решил казнить трусов, командовавших провальной атакой на цитадель Детей Источника. В ответ вся армия взбунтовалась и изгнала его на заброшенную орбитальную станцию!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_VICTORY</LocID>
        <Text>Агент Молссон, полковник Снифф и героические солдаты Фоссории, это автоматическое сообщение. Все враждебные формы жизни уничтожены. Мёртвы вы или живы - ваша миссия завершена. Поздравляю!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_OBJECTIVE_MAIN</LocID>
        <Text>Разгромить всех врагов!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_OBJECTIVE_MAIN_TEXT</LocID>
        <Text>Настоящее веселье только начинается. База в наших руках. Уничтожим их всех!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_OBJECTIVE_MAIN_SNIF</LocID>
        <Text>Прямо как в старые добрые времена!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_SUPREME1</LocID>
        <Text>Я предупреждал тебя не раз, Снифф. Ты слишком далеко зашел! Не жди от меня помощи - теперь разбирайся сам!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_SNIF1</LocID>
        <Text>Но, командир, вы же знаете - я уничтожил тех фоссорианцев во имя народа Фоссории!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_SUPREME2</LocID>
        <Text>Болван! Пока ты гниешь на орбите, наши войска гибнут под натиском этих отбросов Детей Источника и мятежников, которых ты же и создал! Тебе крышка!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_SNIF2</LocID>
        <Text>Это не последнее, что ты от меня услышишь!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_SUPREME3</LocID>
        <Text>С нетерпением жду новостей, как наша зачистка найдёт твой труп!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_BROKEN_TELEPORT_SNIF1</LocID>
        <Text>Этот телепорт неисправен. Честно, мне повезло, что он не вывернул мои кишки наизнанку, как носок, когда меня в него затолкали!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_MEET_MOLSON1</LocID>
        <Text>Hey Snif. I picked up signs of a battle, and when I come over to have a look, who do I bump into? Are you involved in another mess again?</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_MEET_SNIF1</LocID>
        <Text>Hi Molsson! Well, yeah. You know me, always knee-deep in crap. But how did you get here? I thought only the rebels and our enemies remained on the planet surface. </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_MEET_MOLSON2</LocID>
        <Text><![CDATA[Old Supreme send me with reinforcements a few cycles ago. But enough talk, we have quite a problem down there. <color=SOTS_COLOR_INDIGO>The Children of The Source</color> are attacking from the south, and the <color=SOTS_COLOR_BRONZE>Fossorian rebels</color> are not far behind.\n\nIf you help me get rid of them all, I'll arrange a ticket for you out of this mess. Deal?]]></Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_MEET_SNIF2</LocID>
        <Text>I'd rather die in battle than die of boredom up here. Deal!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_MEET_MOLSON3</LocID>
        <Text>Follow me!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_MEATBOY1</LocID>
        <Text>What do we have here? A pighead in a shiny uniform who thinks he's the boss around here?</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_MEATBOY_SNIF1</LocID>
        <Text>Get out of the way, you pests!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_EARTHSHAKER1</LocID>
        <Text>Oh, you must be the famous colonel who tried to deal with our incompetent leaders down there! We were banished too! It would be super awesome if we could join you.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_EARTHSHAKER_SNIF1</LocID>
        <Text>Yes, that was me. I'll consider your request.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_HAMMER1</LocID>
        <Text>Where do you think you're going, hotshot?</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_HAMMER_SNIF1</LocID>
        <Text>Screw you! I've got some business with Molsson down on the planet's surface.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_HAMMER2</LocID>
        <Text>Screw me?! You don't screw with Hammerite's screws, you scumbag! No way I'm letting you through!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_LIBERATOR_SNIFF1</LocID>
        <Text>Join me and you won't regret it!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_LIBERATOR1</LocID>
        <Text>RrRrRrRrRrRrRr!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_LIBERATOR_SNIFF2</LocID>
        <Text>I will take it for "Yes colonel, it will be an honor!"</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_KEEPER1</LocID>
        <Text>Hello, commander. As you surely know, I am one of the Keepers. We selflessly care about the wellbeing of ordinary people. Now, let me be blunt: today I am looking for a sword for hire.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_KEEPER2</LocID>
        <Text>Crystal lizards infested some nearby areas. Be careful! When exposed to daylight, they can shoot deadly beams of energy. At night, they can only attack with their teeth and become vulnerable. Although I was a warrior myself, I'm too rusty to beat them on my own.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_KEEPER3</LocID>
        <Text>I know the position of two lizard packs, you'll have to find the last one on your own. If you manage to defeat all of them, I'll give you 10,000 aura coins and plenty of resources.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_KEEPER3_LOCATION1</LocID>
        <Text>Lizard pack in the west canyon.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_KEEPER3_LOCATION2</LocID>
        <Text>The second one is in the Primals ruins.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_KEEPER4</LocID>
        <Text>All the crystal lizards have been dealt with. Return to me to collect your reward!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_KEEPER5</LocID>
        <Text>Excellent, the task is completed. Here is your reward.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_KEEPER6</LocID>
        <Text>The task is completed. Hmmmmmmm, did you really defeat all the crystal lizards by yourself, or has someone else finished them off?</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_KEEPER6_COOMANDER</LocID>
        <Text>Of course, I did it.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_KEEPER7</LocID>
        <Text>Liar! I had plenty of gold and resources for you, but for your deceit, you'll receive only one fusion core.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_KEEPER8</LocID>
        <Text>Next time, think twice before you try to lie to me!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_SIDEQUEST_NONE</LocID>
        <Text>Thank you for your help! I ask nothing more, my friend.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_SIDEQUEST_NOT_DONE_YET</LocID>
        <Text>I told you to deal with all the crystal lizards! Remember?</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_SIDEQUEST_DONE_UNVISIT</LocID>
        <Text>Hello, commander. As you surely know, I am one of the Keepers. We selflessly care about wellbeing of ordinary people. I was looking for a sword for hire to deal with crystal lizards. They have already been slain, but the birds tweeted that at least some of them by your hand.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_SIDEQUEST_DONE_UNVISIT_REW</LocID>
        <Text>Please accept this as an expression of my gratitude.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_SIDEQUEST_TO_LATE</LocID>
        <Text>Hello, commander. As you surely know, I am one of the Keepers. We selflessly care about wellbeing of ordinary people. I was looking for a sword for hire to deal with crystal lizards. They have already been slain, but the birds tweeted that none of them by your hand. Thank you for coming by, anyway!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_SIDEQUEST_DONE_UNVISIT_REW_FULL</LocID>
        <Text>Hello, commander. As you surely know, I am one of the Keepers. We selflessly care about the well-being of ordinary people. I was looking for a sword for hire to deal with crystal lizards. You slain them before you even heard about this job. Although we are not bound by any contract I will give you the full reward anyway as proof that there are still people who want the best for Siren System regardless of profit or politics.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_KEEPER_OBJ</LocID>
        <Text>All the crystal lizards must be defeated 0/3 ! </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_KEEPER_OBJ1</LocID>
        <Text>All the crystal lizards must be defeated 1/3 ! </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_KEEPER_OBJ2</LocID>
        <Text>All the crystal lizards must be defeated 2/3 ! </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_KEEPER_OBJ_DONE</LocID>
        <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GREEN>All the crystal lizards must be defeated 3/3 - DONE</color>]]></Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <!--Gen Truda-->
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_GENTRUDA_SNIFF1</LocID>
        <Text>I am back!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_GENTRUDA_GENTRUDA1</LocID>
        <Text>Well, well, well, aren't you like a dry poo on my shoe? Tough to get rid of. </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_GENTRUDA_ALL</LocID>
        <Text>Oi, rebel! Fossorian justice awaits! </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_GENTRUDA_GENTRUDA2</LocID>
        <Text>If I got an aura coin every time I heard that I would be richer than the Old Supreme Prick! </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_CLOCKI_ALL</LocID>
        <Text>Finally! The leader of the Children of the Source! Tonight I will drink beer from a tin can made of your recycled body! </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_NEXTFEST_CLOCKI_CLOCKI1</LocID>
        <Text>Filthy barbarian! You shall choke on this tin can! </Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <!--end SL message-->
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_END_SUPREME1</LocID>
        <Text>Both enemies were defeated! Not bad! Shame, I´ve already ordered a planetary bombardment! If you accidentally survive, call me. I may have use for you after all!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_SECOND_BROKEN_TELEPORT_All</LocID>
        <Text>No way I am turning this broken orbital teleport on! It would probably shred me into a million pieces!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <!--crusaders defeated-->
      <!-- ??? -->
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_CRUSADES_DEFEATED_SUPREME1</LocID>
        <Text>The Children of the Source have been defeated, but the cost of this campaign is already astronomical! And I did not even count the loss of the rebel army you are also responsible for! I'm never gonna financially recover from this! Now, eradicate the rebels! Fail and I will finish you personally.</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
      <!--fossorian rebels defeated-->
      <GameDBLocalizedString>
        <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_DEMO_REBELS_DEFEATED_SUPREME1</LocID>
        <Text>Finally, the rebels have been punished! And now to the real job! Remember the task I've sent you to do in the first place? Send the Children of the Source to their mad Goddess!</Text>
      </GameDBLocalizedString>
    </LocalizedStrings>
  </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>