<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_HU_EMPIRE">

        <LanguageRef>LANG_HU</LanguageRef>

        <Contributors>
            <Name>Oxymoron Games</Name>
        </Contributors>

        <LocalizedStrings>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>FACTION_EMPIRE</LocID>                    <Text>United Nations of the Solar System (UNSS)</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!--Unit names-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_SCOUT</LocID>                <Text>Volt</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_SCOUT_UPG</LocID>            <Text>Bolt</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
<!--            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_SOLDIER</LocID>              <Text>Trooper</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_SOLDIER_UPG</LocID>          <Text>Veteran Trooper</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_AR84</LocID>                 <Text>Number 6</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_AR84_UPG</LocID>             <Text>Number 6-M</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_VANQUISHER</LocID>           <Text>Crowd Suppressor</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_VANQUISHER_UPG</LocID>       <Text>Crowd Crusher</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_SNIPER</LocID>               <Text>Fifty CAL </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_SNIPER_UPG</LocID>           <Text>Sixty CAL</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
<!--            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_BEAST</LocID>                <Text>Ares</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_BEAST_UPG</LocID>            <Text>Ares MK2</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
<!--            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_WARMACHINE</LocID>           <Text>Titan</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_WARMACHINE_UPG</LocID>       <Text>Titan shield bearer</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_WAR_MACHINE_SHIELD_BLOCK_PROJECTILES</LocID>                 <Text>Ballistic Shield</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_WAR_MACHINE_SHIELD_BLOCK_PROJECTILES_DESCRIPTION</LocID>     <Text><![CDATA[Generates an impenetrable barrier for enemy projectiles.]]></Text></GameDBLocalizedString>


           <!--Unit description-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_SCOUT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                  <Text>The biggest Volt factories are usually built in colonies and are known to have the best working conditions. If you want to oppress someone, let them benefit from that oppression. It will take a long time until they realizes it and they seldom do anything against it. </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_SCOUT_UPG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>              <Text>Dispatching humans is pretty costly, thus Volts became the police force in most C-class neighborhoods. Crime statistics have never been so low, but maybe the people just stopped calling for help. They learned that only these stupid robots will arrive and tase everybody at the scene, regardless of whether they are doing anything illegal or not. </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <!--<GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_SOLDIER_DESCRIPTION</LocID>            <Text>We have guided missiles, plasma rifles, RP drones, sonic rams and a load of vehicles of different tonnage, but most of the time we will just send the Troopers. You know, cost-effectiveness.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_SOLDIER_UPG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>            <Text>Everyone can tell you that UNSS Troopers wear protective spacesuits with basic life support and a fair share of affordable ballistic protection. But no one can truly describe that sweaty, itchy sensation in all of the wrong places at once. </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_AR84_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                   <Text>Number 5 was a huge success, but its AI was too kind-hearted for UNSS military service. Soldiers were simply too tired of its constant whining over dead enemies: "Reassemble him, reassemble him!" "It's freaking DEAD, move along already, you useless tin can!". But NO, they just stood there feeling sad and sorry. </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_AR84_UPG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>               <Text>Along with weapon and armor upgrades, a SW update got installed. Now it will say "neutralized" instead of "killed" and shout "weapon" instead of "that bastard is still alive, shoot his head off!". It's much more humane this way. </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_VANQUISHER_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Do you remember those fargile supermarket guards you could take down with one punch? Why do they even contract such weaklings? Only a few people know that those guards have a little box with a big button that summons the real-deal, face-tattooed, mental, meathead cavalry. In the UNSS, the crowd suppressor unit is this cavalry. </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_VANQUISHER_UPG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>         <Text>The UNSS PR Division is something like the police of old. Back then, most people joined them because they genuinely liked people and they wanted to help society. And then there was the rest. The Crowd Crushers only employ that rest.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_SNIPER_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                 <Text>The longest-serving anti-material caliber cartridge. Because who cares about the enemy, the solid wall he is hiding behind, and the forcefield that stops all regular projectiles!? You know, when you punch that field hard enough, it will overload and collapse. Yee-haa! In your face, you shield-bearing cowards! </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_SNIPER_UPG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>The bigger the stick, the fewer hits are needed to beat down an opponent. The moment when Homo Sapiens adopted this strategy was the beginning of the end for Homo not-so-Sapiens. </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
<!--            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_BEAST_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                  <Text>The invention of Force-shield technology led to a melee combat renaissance. Even now, when ranged weapons started to catch up, military droids rely on trusty old power-blades. These beauties have served for almost 30 years now.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_BEAST_UPG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>              <Text>First, everybody feared serving with them because there was no kill switch or any "backdoor" for remote control. If there weas, the Ares would be too much of an easy prey for hackers. Despite this, there has been not a single incident. The Hesperidians are really good AI programmers. </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
<!--            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_WARMACHINE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Ask any UNSS kid about their dream job. It's always a garbage man, a paleontologist, or a Titan pilot. Then, as an adult, nobody wants to work exposed to the weather or kneel in dirt all day. Soon, the paleontologists will join the extinct species, while the Titans still kick ass!</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_WARMACHINE_UPG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>         <Text>The success of the Ares started a debate over the replacement of human pilots of the Titans. This never happened only because it is elevating the recruitment rates for all military branches. See, most people who enlist and hope to become Titan pilots end up in "other positions". For example a frontline position. </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>

            
            <!--Unit abilities-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ABILITY_UNIT_SCOUT_UPG_SPECIAL</LocID>                      <Text>Chain lightning that strikes targeted enemy unit as well as all enemies on neighbouring hexes.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ABILITY_UNIT_EMPIRE_SOLDIER_UPG_SPECIAL</LocID>             <Text>Hits multiple enemies with lower damage, using special ammunition that causes a bleeding effect.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_AR84_INFO_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                   <Text>Can move and shoot.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ABILITY_UNIT_EMPIRE_AR84_UPG_SPECIAL</LocID>                <Text>Shoots exploding projectiles.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_VANQUISHER_UPG_INFO_DESCRIPTION</LocID>         <Text>Knocks back enemy units.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_SNIPER_INFO_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                 <Text>Shoots precisely at long range, gets a penalty when shooting nearby targets.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_SNIPER_UPG_INFO_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Counters ranged attacks. Shoots precisely at long range, gets a penalty when shooting nearby targets.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_BEAST_PASSIVE_INFO_DESCRIPTION</LocID>          <Text>Can jump over obstacles.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ABILITY_UNIT_EMPIRE_BEAST_UPG_SPECIAL</LocID>               <Text>Hits all enemies around.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_BEAST_PASSIVE_INFO_DESCRIPTION</LocID>          <Text>Can jump over obstacles.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_EMPIRE_WARMACHINE_UPG_INFO_DESCRIPTION</LocID>         <Text>Automatically activates a shield that makes him immune to ranged attacks until it attacks or counters. Can attack up to 3 enemies standing next to each other.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>



            <!--Hero names-->

<!--        <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_1</LocID>     <Text>John Smith 7A</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_2</LocID>     <Text>Capt. Rao</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_3</LocID>     <Text>Navigator Maya</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_4</LocID>     <Text>Doctor Brown 9B</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_5</LocID>     <Text>"Sarge" Zagloba</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_6</LocID>     <Text>Michael Moore 3C </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_7</LocID>     <Text>Henry Williams 2B</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_8</LocID>     <Text>Rob "Scotty"</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_9</LocID>     <Text>Rosie Hart</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_10</LocID>    <Text>Kim Procházka</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_11</LocID>    <Text>General Takeshi</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_12</LocID>    <Text>Admiral Nyota</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_13</LocID>    <Text>Major Zolzaya </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_14</LocID>    <Text>Gahiji Jackson</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_15</LocID>    <Text>Adela</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_16</LocID>    <Text>Governor Burke</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!--Hero description-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_1_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                 <Text>Hesperidian anthropologists studied the human culture based on years of broadcast that spread through space even before the Hesperidian generation ship finished its journey to the Solar System. Smith's understanding of humans made him a master manipulator. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_2_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                 <Text>Captain Arjun Rao comes from one of many arti-satellites of the Saturn belt. As a young man, he managed to get a stipend at the UNSS Military Academy. He truly believes that the UNSS is here to make the world a better place. True believers are dangerous men capable of great things. Both good and terrible. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_3_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                 <Text>The new generation of UNSS personnel was brought up in a world strongly affected by Hesperidian culture, philosophy, and religion. Since the dawn of humanity, all younger generations are a little bit alien to older people, but her generation is weirder than most. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_4_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                 <Text>Doctor Brown was involved in nearly all the inhumane research of the last decades. Mainly studies involving engrams and true AI development. Later, he capitalized on those experiences when working on UNSS Ranock, the strongest ship of the UNSS fleet. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_5_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                 <Text>Highly decorated officer but most medals are made of kebab, curry, and gravy. UNSS army is about order and discipline. So it is a complete enigma of why Andrzej Zagloba enlisted and how he managed to become a sergeant.  </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_6_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                 <Text>The chief astrophysicist of the Expedition fleet sent by the UNSS to explore the Siren System. His obsession with Greek mythology has not only maifested itself in the name of the Siren system, but is also to blame for the names of the planets and countless other things. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_7_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                 <Text>For 2B, the arrival to the Solar System meant a fall from grace. Hesperidian technicians lost their priviledged status as the survival of their species was no longer in their hands. Although he requalified and later joined the Expedition fleet as a xenotechnologist, some of the bitterness over the lost importance lasts. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_8_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                 <Text>This tall highlander with a strong accent comes from the fog-covered peaks of the NN-York scrapyard. It is remarkable how many UNSS officers with non-UNSS backgrounds volunteered for the Siren System expeditionary force. Almost as if they had "second class" written on their forehead. But, who would not want a fresh start? </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_9_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                 <Text>Usually, the spoiled brats of wealthy families join the Sovereighn as a part of their "rebellion", but Rosie is a different type of "brat". Although she was born with a silver spoon in hand, she enlisted for the Trooper Core. Joining the military as a revolt, isn't that quite oxymoronic? </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_10_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                <Text>A former student of the famous professor Zane. Procházka dedicated his life to getting admitted to an exclusively Hesperidian Research Division. After years of effort, he is still a lab assistant, but he is the only human who ever made it so far. A testament to his superior intellect. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_11_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                <Text>Famous for a quote commenting on the victory over Sovereign Colonies: "The Hesperidian involvement in the war was one of the greatest achievements of the UNSS and one of the biggest mistakes of humanity". His career only survived because Hesperidians were not good with words yet, back then.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_12_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                <Text>There were several "iron ladies" in human history and none of them was given this nickname for their gentle attitude and peaceful nature. No wonder the Hesperidians supported her appointment as the commanding officer of the Expedition Fleet heading for the Siren System. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_13_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                <Text>Her unit is called the "Sovereign Hunters" and gets deployed whenever the atmosphere in some colony reaches the boiling point. They are experts in "cooling" the "hot heads". Most often they cool them down to −270 °C (or −455 °F), the temperature of space. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_14_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                <Text>Gahigi is a commando-type that eats green berets for breakfast. He is tough, strong, an excellent shooter, and a tactical prodigy. But he is still going to action with his troops and has declined all promotions. Maybe he is scared that a higher rank would imprison him at the office. And he is right, the system does not work! </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_15_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                <Text>She is in the Secret Service. Everybody knows that. The problem is, nobody knows in which one and what her rank is. Therefore, everybody is pre-emptively scared of her, which gives her that special femme fatale aura - and also acts as a friend repellent. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_EMPIRE_16_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                <Text>If the concept of bureaucracy materialized into an avatar, his name would be Burke and he would serve as a governor of a UNSS colony. He is an efficient, precise, and a capable commander. Shame that he will not make a move without proper authorization. Not even if his mother was drowning. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
<!-- and their encyclopedic knowledg of the ship-universe lost the critical importance. -->
<!-- Hesperidians are bastards. They are rude, imperious and consider humans as bio-robots appropriate only for labour and combat, and are terrible to small animals. You would expect there is always at least one exception and that this exception is Michael Moore 3C. Keep expecing -->
        </LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
