<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_PATCH_08_MAPS">

        <LanguageRef>LANG_EN</LanguageRef>

        <Contributors>
            <Name>Oxymoron Games</Name>
        </Contributors>

        <LocalizedStrings>
            <!--BLUE BORDER-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_BLUE_BORDER</LocID>                                      <Text>Blue border</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_BLUE_BORDER_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                          <Text>The blue lowlands in the middle of the map, a sacred neutral territory, are also an open path to your enemies.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_BLUE_BORDER_INTRO</LocID>                                <Text>Not so long ago, a brutal war raged here. The Clerics, caught in the middle of it all, could no longer keep up with healing the wounded. With the help of environmental engineers, they secured an area in the shape of a cross, marked by literally coloring the surface blue. \n\nWhile it was originally meant to serve as a safe place for evacuating and treating the injured, after the war it became much more: a symbol of neutrality that divides the hostile territories.\n\nEventually, the wounded were gone, colors have faded and the Clerics have left. Now the path lies open once again if anybody decides to break the peace.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_BLUE_BORDER_VICTORY</LocID>                              <Text>The symbol of neutrality and aid did not stop you. Even though you've achieved victory, it's a shameful victory.</Text>    </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <!--SUDDEN DEATH-->                                                                          
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_SUDDEN_DEATH</LocID>                                     <Text>Sudden death</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_SUDDEN_DEATH_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                         <Text>Eight enemies, very close to each other. The paths between you are unobstructed. Good luck!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_SUDDEN_DEATH_INTRO</LocID>                               <Text>An overgrown land, rich in resources, got colonised by various factions. Right from the start, they agreed on a non-aggression pact, built roads between each other, and trade flourished. But it only took a tiny spark and war got declared between everybody. The roads remain unguarded, and former good neighbors have become bloodthirsty enemies.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_SUDDEN_DEATH_VICTORY</LocID>                             <Text>You slaughtered them all — once your good neighbors and trading partners. Well, history is written by the victors and it clearly says you were an innocent victim of foreign aggression!</Text>    </GameDBLocalizedString>
        </LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
