<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_PATCH_01">

        <LanguageRef>LANG_EN</LanguageRef>

        <Contributors>
            <Name>Oxymoron Games</Name>
        </Contributors>

        <LocalizedStrings>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>        <LocID>FRIENDLY</LocID>                                                      <Text>Friendly</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>        <LocID>WILL_NOT_NEGOTIATE</LocID>                                            <Text>Will never negotiate</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>        <LocID>ICON_UNIT_RESIST</LocID>                                              <Text>Resist</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>        <LocID>OPTION_GRAPHICS_RESOLUTION_SCALE</LocID>                              <Text>Resolution scale (map)</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>        <LocID>HEADING_OBJECTIVES_CAMPAIGN</LocID>                                   <Text>What lies ahead:</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>        <LocID>COOLDOWN</LocID>                                                      <Text>Cooldown</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>        <LocID>COOLDOWN_ROUNDS</LocID>                                               <Text>rounds</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>        <LocID>MAIN_MENU_EARLY_ACESS</LocID>                                         <Text>Thanks for playing the Early Access version of Silence of the Siren! \n\nWe appreciate your support for the game before its full release and we hope you'll have a lot of fun with the included content. \n\nWe're looking forward to reciving your feedback and bug reports and we're working hard on improving the game based on the community input. \n\nLinks to the bug reporting section on the Steam forum and to our Discord are below.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!--_______________MAP_BRIDGES_TOO_FAR__________________________-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_BRIDGES_TOO_FAR_ID</LocID>                                        <Text>Bridges too far</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_BRIDGES_TOO_FAR_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                               <Text><![CDATA[The last two bridges connect the divided landscape; will the <b>Fossorians</b> or the <b>Children of the Source</b> find them first?]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_BRIDGES_TOO_FAR_INTRO</LocID>                                     <Text>Hello Commander, the line of contact with the enemy is permanently broken. Scouts are reporting that there are only two bridges left. Acquire at least one Fusion core, use it to activate any of the bridges, reach and defeat the enemy before they do the same to you.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_BRIDGES_TOO_FAR_VICTORY</LocID>                                   <Text>While bridges usually connect and unify, now a bridge has opened the path for destruction and devastation.</Text>    </GameDBLocalizedString>


            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_BRIDGES_TOO_FAR_KEEPER_0</LocID>                             <Text>Greetings, commander! I am with the Keepers Guild. My brother, who is also a member, and I have been living here for an eternity. We started to get bored and play pranks on each other.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_BRIDGES_TOO_FAR_KEEPER_1</LocID>                             <Text>I want you to bring back the artifact that my brother hid from me. I can't get to it myself because he set dangerous creatures around it. I had the path to it blocked with stones for safety, but now it's clear for you. I will reward you generously.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_BRIDGES_TOO_FAR_KEEPER_2</LocID>                             <Text>I see that you haven't retrieved the artifact yet. Come back once you have it.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_BRIDGES_TOO_FAR_KEEPER_3</LocID>                             <Text>Thank you for retrieving my artifact. With little effort, I have outsmarted my brother once again. You can keep the artifact; I believe it will be safer with you.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_BRIDGES_TOO_FAR_KEEPER_4</LocID>                             <Text>And here is your reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_BRIDGES_TOO_FAR_KEEPER_5</LocID>                             <Text>I haven't come up with any new pranks for my brother yet.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>


            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_BRIDGES_TOO_FAR_KEEPER</LocID>                             <Text>Acquire the guarded artifact.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_BRIDGES_TOO_FAR_KEEPER1</LocID>                            <Text>Return to the Keeper for your reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!--_______________MAP_CRYING_RIVER__________________________-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_CRYING_RIVER_ID</LocID>                                           <Text>Crying river</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_CRYING_RIVER_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                                  <Text><![CDATA[The old dry river creates a barrier that splits the landscape into three territories. Will the <b>Fossorians</b>, the <b>Children of the Source</b> or the <b>Sovereign fleet</b> unite all territories under one rule?]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_CRYING_RIVER_INTRO</LocID>                                        <Text>Hello Commander, we have established small base in the area. Our intelligence services advise us about possible multiple enemies, so stay sharp. Your task is to build a strong base, gather as many troops as possible, search and destroy all enemies and take over all territory.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_CRYING_RIVER_VICTORY</LocID>                                      <Text>Obviously, this territory was also important to our enemies. Thnak to you, commander, it is fully under our control.</Text>    </GameDBLocalizedString>
                                                                                                                  
                                                                                                                  
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRYING_RIVER_KEEPER_0</LocID>                                <Text>Greetings, commander! I am with the Keepers Guild. Do you see the land around? It was once full of life, full of joy... \nSuch a rich country, thanks to the profits coming from orbital mines... \nNow there are only a few old miners surviving down here. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRYING_RIVER_KEEPER_1</LocID>                                <Text>I am old and it is often very difficult to look on the bright side of life. I have lost my precious Magnesium torch somewhere in the old mines. If you find it and bring it to me, I will reward you generously.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRYING_RIVER_KEEPER_2</LocID>                                <Text>I see that you haven't find the Magnesium torch yet. Come back once you have it.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRYING_RIVER_KEEPER_3</LocID>                                <Text>I didn't believe that you could find it... I am truly impressed! \nYou can keep it, even your young eyes might need some extra help when exploring dark places...</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRYING_RIVER_KEEPER_4</LocID>                                <Text>And here is your reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRYING_RIVER_KEEPER_5</LocID>                                <Text>There is nothing you could do for an old miner like me.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
                                                                                                                  
                                                                                                                  
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_CRYING_RIVER_KEEPER</LocID>                                <Text>Bring back the lost Magnesium torch.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_CRYING_RIVER_KEEPER1</LocID>                               <Text>Return to the Keeper for your reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <!--LOADING TIPS TEXTS-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>LOADING_TIP_01</LocID>                                               <Text>Sometimes it is better to attack a stronger army (moderate or high hazard) rather than get stuck around your base.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>LOADING_TIP_02</LocID>                                               <Text>It can pay off to secure sufficient income before investing in production of units.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>LOADING_TIP_03</LocID>                                               <Text>In combat, you can use one Commander Ability each round, as long as you have enough energy.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>LOADING_TIP_04</LocID>                                               <Text>Be careful when attacking with your limited range units! If you get too close, your unit will receive a counter-attack like a melee unit would.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>LOADING_TIP_05</LocID>                                               <Text>Some objects on the exploration map create zones inflicting positive or negative effects in their vicinity. Watch your step!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>LOADING_TIP_06</LocID>                                               <Text>Don't forget to use your consumables when the time is right! For example when you are one step away from catching your enemy.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>LOADING_TIP_07</LocID>                                               <Text>Moving units between commanders costs move points, so plan your army mergers carefully!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>LOADING_TIP_08</LocID>                                               <Text>All factions have a way to unlock fast travel between bases.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>LOADING_TIP_09</LocID>                                               <Text>When you don't have access to one specific resource, you can always buy some of it at your trading post.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>LOADING_TIP_10</LocID>                                               <Text>When fighting local fauna, make sure you're approaching the creatures at the right time when they are most vulnerable!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>LOADING_TIP_11</LocID>                                               <Text>War machines that you can build at each base are expensive, but can become a game changer.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>LOADING_TIP_12</LocID>                                               <Text>If weird things keep happening around you and some actions seem too easy, you probably have a special skill or an artifact.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!--_______________EQUIPMENT__________________________-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EQUIPMENT_SUBDERMAL_ARMOR_DESCRIPTION_V2</LocID>                     <Text><![CDATA[Increases the <color=SOTS_COLOR_BLUE>Defense</color> of bio units, based on the unit's level.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EQUIPMENT_SMARTGUN_AIMING_UNIT_DESCRIPTION_V2</LocID>                <Text><![CDATA[Grants bonus <color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>Damage</color> to <color=SOTS_COLOR_ATTACK>ranged attacks</color> based on the unit's level.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EQUIPMENT_SIDEARM_DESCRIPTION_V2</LocID>                             <Text><![CDATA[Grants extra <color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>Melee Damage</color> to <color=SOTS_COLOR_ATTACK>ranged units</color> based on the unit's level.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EQUIPMENT_RECON_DRONE_DESCRIPTION_V2</LocID>                         <Text><![CDATA[Increases the commander's <color=SOTS_COLOR_MOVEMENT>visibility</color> range.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EQUIPMENT_MEDAL_OF_HONOR_DESCRIPTION_V2</LocID>                      <Text><![CDATA[This old trinket increases the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Morale</color> of your troops <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>by 10</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EQUIPMENT_CEREMONIAL_FLAG_DESCRIPTION_V2</LocID>                     <Text><![CDATA[Increases the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Morale</color> of your troops <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>by 5</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CONSUMABLE_MAGNESIUM_TORCH_DESCRIPTION_V2</LocID>                    <Text><![CDATA[Immediately reveals a large area of the <color=SOTS_COLOR_INDIGO>fog of war</color> around the commander.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EQUIPMENT_CAMPAIGN_BEACON</LocID>                                    <Text><![CDATA[Radio Beacon]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EQUIPMENT_CAMPAIGN_BEACON_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                        <Text><![CDATA[A powerful radio wave emitter. Its signal can be even located from the orbit. ]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EQUIPMENT_CAMPAIGN_BEACON_LORE</LocID>                               <Text><![CDATA[Without it, any planetary bombardment would be as precise as a drunkard's description of thermonuclear fusion. Which is not accurate, but surprisingly, it is not terrible either (on a planetary scale). But still, you may hit Slovenia instead of Slovakia.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EQUIPMENT_CAMPAIGN_BEACON_II</LocID>                                 <Text><![CDATA["Radio Beacon"]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EQUIPMENT_CAMPAIGN_BEACON_II_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                     <Text><![CDATA[A portable nuclear weapon disguised as a radio wave emitter.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EQUIPMENT_CAMPAIGN_BEACON_II_LORE</LocID>                            <Text><![CDATA[Oh yes, it is definitely a "radio beacon". But seriously, we all know better this time. A nuclear weapon like this is a gift. A gift to the foes of the Supreme Leader and his regime. ]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EQUIPMENT_CAMPAIGN_RELIC</LocID>                                     <Text><![CDATA[The Relic]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EQUIPMENT_CAMPAIGN_RELIC_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                         <Text><![CDATA[An ancient artifact. Its origin and purpose is unknown.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EQUIPMENT_CAMPAIGN_RELIC_LORE</LocID>                                <Text><![CDATA[The item is stylized to look like an insect larva with a malevolent smile. Its origin or purpose is unknown, but with a design like this, it's hard to imagine it had a mundane purpose. I wouldn't take a cookie from a jar like this, would you? By the way, it is emitting strong theta waves. ]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
           
            <!--_______________ABILITIES__________________________-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ABILITY_HERO_COMBAT_HACK_DESCRIPTION_LVL2_V2</LocID>                 <Text>The unit is Hypnotized and cannot move.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ABILITY_HERO_COMBAT_MIMICKING_TACTICS_DESCRIPTION_V2</LocID>         <Text>Mimics (transforms into) any unit on the battlefield.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
        </LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
