<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_INVENTORY_ITEMS_EXPLORATION_ARTIFACTS">

        <LanguageRef>LANG_EN</LanguageRef>

        <Contributors>
            <Name>Oxymoron Games</Name>
        </Contributors>

        <LocalizedStrings>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_VAGRANT</LocID>                                 <Text>Vagrant</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_VAGRANT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                     <Text><![CDATA[An artifact.\nAdds <color=SOTS_COLOR_MOVEMENT>10 Movement Points</color> for each turn.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString><!--TODO put back when short cuts are done ->All shortcuts will be gratis and instant.-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_VAGRANT_LORE</LocID>                            <Text>Sometimes all it takes is to keep moving. And if your will breaks, the Vagrant doesn't allow you to stop. Whether you drive, ride, run, or totter on bloody stumps does not matter. It is not your call anymore.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_SEER</LocID>                                    <Text>Seer</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_SEER_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                        <Text>An artifact.\nPermanently raises the commander's visibility range every cycle.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_SEER_LORE</LocID>                               <Text>It begins with pictures from the past that don't belong to you. Then the whole world becomes one big deja-vu and after a while, you realize you've already walked the same paths before. Countless times. Everything you see belongs to the Seer now.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_MOONWALKER</LocID>                              <Text>MoonWalker</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_MOONWALKER_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                  <Text>An artifact.\nDuring the night, it will remove the fog of war from a vast area around the commander. Vision bonus +3. During the day the commander's atribute vision will return to normal.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_MOONWALKER_LORE</LocID>                         <Text>You are recognizing the slightest differences in texture, material, and movements of the shadows now. Give it a weak and you'll probably start to understand the vampires a lot more. After a month you'll probably start to look like one of them too.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_PHOENIX</LocID>                                 <Text>Phoenix</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_PHOENIX_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                     <Text>An artifact.\nRetreating commander will appear in the nearest empty base with half of their army, with XP gained in battle with all their gear.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString> <!-- TODO (Should the artefact disapear afterwards)? -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_PHOENIX_LORE</LocID>                            <Text>The instinct of self-preservation is strong, but merging with the Phoenix is a whole new chapter. Your entire being becomes dedicated to survival. Forget the oaths, orders, friends, loved ones. Yearning for life is infectious. Let's run, let's live!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_SITE_CONSCIOUSNESS</LocID>                      <Text>Site Consciousness</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_SITE_CONSCIOUSNESS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>          <Text><![CDATA[An artifact.\nGrants <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>usage</color> of <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Globetrotter</color> abilities <color=SOTS_COLOR_MOVEMENT>twice</color> per phase (Different ones).]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_SITE_CONSCIOUSNESS_LORE</LocID>                 <Text>With a little bit of self-discipline, no one will recognize that your consciousness was grafted and is currently operating on several battle plans at once. Like a room full of seasoned generals but better! Because they are you and nobody laughs at your convoluted plans.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_MASTERMIND</LocID>                              <Text>Mastermind</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_MASTERMIND_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                  <Text><![CDATA[An artifact.\n<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Permanently</color> raises <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Ability Strength</color> attribute by <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>1</color> each <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>cycle</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ARTIFACT_MASTERMIND_LORE</LocID>                         <Text>Close your eyes. Focuse. Oh yes, you can already feel it grow! Your mind capacity of course, what did you think? Bicep? That would be actually nice too but though muscles can be helpful in any fight, a brilliant mind can change the outcome of the whole battle.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

        </LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
