<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_PATCH_DOOM_OF_EDEN">

        <LanguageRef>LANG_EN</LanguageRef>

        <Contributors>
            <Name>Oxymoron Games</Name>
        </Contributors>

        <LocalizedStrings>

            <!--_______________EA DOOM OF EDEN MAP__________________________-->

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_INTRO_01</LocID>                           <Text>Hi, my name is Rosie, and as the owner, I would like to welcome you to the top-secret recreational resort, Eden.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_INTRO_02</LocID>                           <Text>Besides relaxing in one of our wellness facilities, you can go on an evening safari, enjoy breathtaking views of the surrounding jungle, and next year, we'll even start building a water park!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_INTRO_03</LocID>                           <Text>You've chosen a great time to visit, as autumn has just begun, and the leaves on the trees are starting to change into vibrant colors ... oh, wait!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_INTRO_04</LocID>                           <Text>It's you! Yes, I've received the orders.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_INTRO_05</LocID>                           <Text>Alright, you can explore the surroundings, hire a few commanders, and construct some buildings, but don't you dare turn this place into a military base or a mining station!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_INTRO_06</LocID>                           <Text>And don't expect me to help you! You're not taking any of my supplies, and I'll be watching your every move!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_INTRO</LocID>                                 <Text>Explore the surroundings.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_BLUE_ALERT</LocID>                            <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_BLUE>BLUE ALERT</color>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_YELLOW_ALERT</LocID>                          <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_YELLOW>YELLOW ALERT</color>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_RED_ALERT</LocID>                             <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>RED ALERT</color>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_LIMERIT</LocID>                            <Text>Really? You want to start mining limerite here? Sure, why not, why not undermine the whole landscape? There's no reason to worry about landslides or the collapse of the terrain.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_FIBER</LocID>                              <Text>Are you sure about this factory? Do you know it releases 19 different oxides? Sure, we'll turn it into a new attraction, who wouldn't want to visit a sauna while wearing a gas mask ...</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_BIOMASS</LocID>                            <Text>It starts with biomass, just tap this with something, modify that over there, and it turns into a biological weapons factory. Then one bat escapes, and we're screwed ...</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_RADIANT</LocID>                            <Text>Are you kidding me? A particle colider? And here? Sure, someone's going to miscalculate again, so why not have our own black hole? Not that it wouldn't be a nice spectacle, just hope someone is still alive to admire it ...</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_GOLDMINE</LocID>                           <Text>If you let me mint our aqua-park money there, I don't have a problem with it. What do you think would be a better symbol for the currency, a dolphin or a shark?</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_SLAVE</LocID>                              <Text>Slaves? Absolutely not! All the refugees working for me do so entirely voluntarily, for minimum wage with no claims for overtime pay. It's better to free them (I mean slaves) so they can help us as soon as possible with the construction of the water park.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_STORAGE</LocID>                            <Text>It's not possible to bury the whole warehouse? Why do I have the feeling this looks like a door to Scrooge McDuck's vault?</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_SMUG</LocID>                               <Text>Smugglers, wanderers, homeless people, junkies ... and all this right behind our house? Either join them or burn it down so I can at least have one less problem to worry about.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_BROTHEL</LocID>                            <Text>A brothel, here? Don't tell me you are one of those perverts who like to watch mole whores dancing on a pole? I didn't have a very high opinion of you, but if you go in there, you'll hit rock bottom with me ...</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_WATCH</LocID>                              <Text>As I've mentioned, you've chosen a great time to visit. Right in front of you stands the observation tower, offering a stunning view of the surrounding landscape. The leaves on the trees are beginning to change into autumn hues, and if you gaze at the distant hills, you will feel your body relax and your mind unwind. The air is fresh, with a natural scent that enhances the experience even further. \nIf you decide to climb to the top, you'll be rewarded with panoramic views that you can enjoy with a hot cup of tea in hand. This moment of tranquility is the perfect way to recharge and take in the beauty of the surrounding nature.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_SKILL</LocID>                              <Text>Welcome to our Skill Academy, a place where passion and the desire for personal development meet. This academy is designed for anyone who wants to improve their skills, whether it's in technical, creative, or strategic areas. Here, you can dive into a wide range of courses and workshops that will not only push you forward but also inspire you to take on new challenges. \nAt the academy, we focus on practical skills that will help you not only in your professional life but also in your personal growth. Our experts will guide you through every step and help you discover and unlock your full potential. \nWhether you're a beginner or an experienced professional, you'll find programs that open up new opportunities for you. Join us and gain the skills that will take you to the next level!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_TOMB</LocID>                               <Text>A Tomb of the Swordmaster? Honestly, I don't get why we even have something like that around. Everything here is about wellness, peace, and relaxation ... and then there's this. It wasn't even built by us. Why would anyone want to think about fighting when they're here to relax? \nThe tomb looks like a toy sword stuck in the ground, certainly not something that should be part of this peaceful environment.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_TRAIN</LocID>                              <Text>When you think it can't get any worse, every morning at dawn some stupid monk starts banging a gong, which can be heard loud and clear, even from our most luxurious apartments. Would you mind asking them if they can swim? They might earn more money as lifeguards ...</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_CONSTRUCTION</LocID>                       <Text>Noooo, don't build anything there! This spot is reserved for our ultra-turbo-galactic waterslide!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_WELL</LocID>                               <Text>A "wishing well," huh? Yeah, not exactly ideal if our guests toss in a coin and end up with a multifunctional blaster.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_BEAST</LocID>                              <Text>Looking for something beyond relaxation and luxury? Welcome to the Beast Nest, the most thrilling attraction our resort has to offer! This unique experience lets you witness, or even take part in battles against some of the most formidable creatures ever encountered. But don't worry, it's not just about the fight. Victors walk away with rare and exclusive rewards, making this a must-visit for those seeking both excitement and treasures. Whether you're here to watch from a safe distance or step into the action yourself, the Beast Nest promises a spectacle like no other. Dare to take a closer look!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_SANTC</LocID>                              <Text>Can someone explain to me why the Children of the Source keep leaving their battle temples and sanctuaries everywhere? How are you supposed to meditate when all you can hear is the constant clashing of metal?</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_ROCKET</LocID>                             <Text>More space junk? Unbelievable. Imagine this, you take a group of noble intergalactic slugs on a peaceful stargazing retreat, and right at the spot where your gourmet food stand is set up, staffed by the only chef in the sector who knows how to prepare crystalline roe, a chunk of a crashed shuttle comes falling from the sky. Being a hotelier isn't easy...</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_GATE</LocID>                               <Text>One of the four gates around here. We never found the keys, but we've tracked them circulating on the black market. Sooner or later, someone's going to show up with them, and I really can't be held responsible if they accidentally fall into the wood chipper.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_CRUSADER_BASE</LocID>                      <Text>Originally, we planned to open centers for high-ranking members of the other factions as well. This particular one had the codename "Hotel exterminator".</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_MOLLES_BASE</LocID>                        <Text>Here, we had a great idea that quickly fell apart a horror experience: stay in the enemy's environment. But relaxation and horror don't mix well ... my mistake. Feel free to take it over.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_PIRATES_BASE</LocID>                       <Text>This is my winter residence. I used to work for the "Sovereign," and I really love their architecture, it reminds me a lot of Gaudí. If you want, it's at your disposal, but don't you dare mess with my fossilized vegetable collection!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_FIREFLI</LocID>                            <Text>Stop! This is the only place in this area where fireflies appear. Usually, you'd find them in the mushroom region, but this is the only exception. It took me seven years to catch all the Luminovores. Did you know that in some areas, people catch, dry, and smoke them? ... you knew, didn't you? Don't even think about it!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_CRYSTAL</LocID>                            <Text>Do you see this beauty? This is the main attraction of our evening safari. At sunset, these magnificent lizards change form. Breathtaking, isn't it? But consider this a warning! If even a single crystal is missing or if they have the tiniest scratch, I'll turn you into an attraction, dress you up in a seal costume and throw you into a cage full of polar bears.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_MUSHROOM</LocID>                           <Text>Look, this is a magical mushroom. If you stay near it for a while, it will start to release spores that induce feelings of happiness and joy. Just be careful, we don't have an antidote yet.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_INTEL</LocID>                              <Text>We've received a message from the secret service – all the raiders have made a non-aggression pact, something along the lines of "first come, first served," which means they're only targeting. That's pretty bad news, I guess ... </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_TELEPORT_01</LocID>                        <Text>A teleport, here? How the hell did it get here? This is not good, I'm doing a quick scan ...</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_TELEPORT_02</LocID>                        <Text><![CDATA[This is very bad! We've detected a total of 8 one-way teleportation devices leading here. I'm initiating a <color=SOTS_COLOR_BLUE>BLUE ALERT</color>!]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_TELEPORT_03</LocID>                        <Text><![CDATA[I take it back, a <color=SOTS_COLOR_BLUE>BLUE ALERT</color> shoud be reserved for an attack by self-inflating giant interdimensional brain-eaters. I'm declaring a <color=SOTS_COLOR_YELLOW>YELLOW ALERT</color>: everybody prepare for incoming threats! ]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_TELEPORT_04</LocID>                        <Text>I have a really bad feeling about this! My life's work, ... well, my quarter-life's work is at risk. It’s possible that this place will soon be swarming with God knows what.\nWe need to prepare an army. I know I haven't been always very kind to you, but please, I beg you, help me protect this place.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_TELEPORT_MONEY</LocID>                     <Text>Here's all our available money and other necessary resources.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>


            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_RED_ALERT</LocID>                          <Text><![CDATA[Here it comes! We've detected the first teleport activation. An enemy will appear soon. I'm declaring a <color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>RED ALERT</color>. Please, destroy anything and anybody that comes through!]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_NEXT_ENEMIES</LocID>                       <Text>Another teleport activation, be ready!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_NEXT_ENEMIES_NEXT</LocID>                  <Text>You're doing great, but I have some bad news for you. It looks like a large group of enemies is still approaching. You deserve a reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_NEXT_ENEMIES_DONE</LocID>                  <Text>Phew, it looks like those were the last ones. We can't waste any time, we need to start rebuilding the area. In a few phases, I'll send units to destroy the teleporters. Take out the remaining enemies and get some rest. Your mission seems to be over. Oh, and before I forget, this is for you:</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_NEXT_ENEMIES_LAST_DANCE</LocID>            <Text>No, absolutely not. This is too much, even for me. The fun ends here, my patience has run out.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_NEXT_ENEMIES_END</LocID>                   <Text>In the name of Eden, now you've really pissed me off, and I'm coming to settle this with you. The breakfast is over, your intestines are on today's lunch menu!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_ROSI_KEY</LocID>                                <Text>Look, the key to the gate. I recommend opening it as soon as possible, it could be a great help to us.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>


            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_FOSSORIANS</LocID>                              <Text>In the name of the Fossorian people, we annex these lands to our territory!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_CRUSADERS</LocID>                               <Text>I declare this territory the property of the Children of the Source. May our wrath be spread across the land!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_PIRATES</LocID>                                 <Text>From now on, let this land be known as the new recreational retreat of the Sovereign Fleet. Objections are not allowed.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_DOOM_OF_EDEN_UNSS</LocID>                                    <Text>I claim this territory ... solely for myself! Anyone who opposes, take cover.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

        </LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
