<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_CUTSCENES">

        <LanguageRef>LANG_EN</LanguageRef>

        <Contributors>
            <Name>Oxymoron Games</Name>
        </Contributors>

        <LocalizedStrings>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_SUBHEADING_1</LocID>                  <Text>Fossorians Chapter 1</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_SUBHEADING_2</LocID>                  <Text>Fossorians Chapter 2</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_SUBHEADING_3</LocID>                  <Text>Fossorians Chapter 3</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_SUBHEADING_4</LocID>                  <Text>Fossorians Chapter 4</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_HEADING_1</LocID>                     <Text>Penal Legion</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_TEXT_1</LocID>                        <Text>Fossorian intelligence discovered some highly unusual activity in a border region. The Children of the Source - a religious order of insectoid cyborgs - are up to something. The trouble is that Fossorians are not officially at war with them.\n\n General Furret, imprisoned after a corruption scandal, was given a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity to join the Penal Legion and reclaim his freedom. \n\nThe task ahead sounds simple: a false-flag operation to carry a radio beacon into the heart of the enemy territory so they can be obliterated from the orbit.\n\n The Fossorians have already secured a bridgehead. It all looks like an easy job. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_HEADING_2</LocID>                     <Text>Prison</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_TEXT_2</LocID>                        <Text>After getting betrayed by the high command and after making their narrow escape from an atomic blast, our two Fossorians fled carrying a mysterious relic.\n\nFor now, everyone thinks they're dead. Otherwise, the Supreme Leader and the Children of the Source would surely want their heads on a spike.\n\nLuckily, Gen Furret knows a smuggler able to sell the relic. The money should buy fuel for their stolen starship and give our 'heroes' a chance to hide in the scarcely populated edge territories.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_HEADING_3</LocID>                     <Text>Old Friends</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_TEXT_3</LocID>                        <Text>After yet another clash with the Children of the Source, our 'heroes' realized that even in the barren edge, they would be discovered again sooner or later.\n\nBut there lies another path. Surrounded by the Fossorian army and protected by the thick walls of the Capital, they would be untouchable. And to top it off, a considerable bonus: Revenge against their hated Supreme Leader! The only catch? The massive loyalist army. But if you know where to look for allies, it may only be a momentary obstacle.\n\nIt will be a long journey from the edge territories to central Fossorian lands, but the only way to contact Admiral Muff's rebel friends is to meet them in person. The rebels barely escaped punishment after the unsuccessful Nemek rebellion. Convincing them to raise arms against the Supreme Leader again won't be easy.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_HEADING_4</LocID>                     <Text>Heart of the Realm</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_TEXT_4</LocID>                        <Text>That's it, the very heart of Fossorian territory and the last bastion of the Supreme Leader. If he stays, he will face the rebel army; if he runs, he will be lost. The challenged ruler's presence in the capital is the only leg left of his legitimacy. The commanders would not recognize the authority of a runaway.\n\nIn the meantime, the rebel army has split. While General Furret leads the ground operations, Admiral Muff navigates the army from the air.\n\nThe only thing that's bothering our 'heroes' is the absence of the Fossorian fleet. The Supreme Leader must question the loyalty of his captains and wants to deny them the chance to turn coat at the height of the battle.   </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_1_OBJECTIVE_1</LocID>                 <Text>Carry a beacon to enemy territory</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_1_OBJECTIVE_2</LocID>                 <Text>Pick up reinforcements for your army</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_2_OBJECTIVE_1</LocID>                 <Text>Free an old friend from prison</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_2_OBJECTIVE_2</LocID>                 <Text>Learn about the Relic you discovered on the stolen ship</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_3_OBJECTIVE_1</LocID>                 <Text>Recruit old Fossorian rebels for your cause</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_3_OBJECTIVE_2</LocID>                 <Text>Open a path to the Central Territories</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_4_OBJECTIVE_1</LocID>                 <Text>Prevail against everything Snif sends at you</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_4_OBJECTIVE_2</LocID>                 <Text>Disable enemy air defenses</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_MOLES_4_OBJECTIVE_3</LocID>                 <Text>Prepare for the final battle!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
        </LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
