<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_CAMPAIGN_CRUSADERS_CUTSCENES">

        <LanguageRef>LANG_EN</LanguageRef>

        <Contributors>
            <Name>Oxymoron Games</Name>
        </Contributors>

        <LocalizedStrings>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_CRUSADERS_SUBHEADING_1</LocID>                  <Text>Children of the Source - Chapter 1</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_CRUSADERS_SUBHEADING_2</LocID>                  <Text>Children of the Source - Chapter 2</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_CRUSADERS_SUBHEADING_3</LocID>                  <Text>Children of the Source - Chapter 3</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_CRUSADERS_SUBHEADING_4</LocID>                  <Text>Children of the Source - Chapter 4</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_CRUSADERS_HEADING_1</LocID>                     <Text>Home alone</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_CRUSADERS_TEXT_1</LocID>                        <Text>Annika is alive!\n\nThere is a catch, though; she has been jailed by the UNSS. But Tin's Sovereign Fleet friends claim a transfer will be ordered soon, and prison transports may easily become victims of a hijack. Especially in the uncharted border regions. \n\nThis information arrives while Tin has been absent, so only a little clone of Allmother and her guardian Viktar know about the transport. \n\nTin may return soon, but the window of opportunity may close at any moment. Now, it's up to our heroes to decide whether act or wait. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CAMPAIGN_CRUSADERS_LVL1_THE_END</LocID>                   <Text>All hopes for Annika's safe return were in vain. At least the Princess will not fall for such a trap again. \n\nOnly by luck, Tin returned in time and tipped the balance of the encounter. Unless the UNSS intervention the UNSS forces would be decimated. \n\nBut there is a consolation prize. The Princess finished her metamorphosis and acquired a new body. A serious blow for the UNSS controlled by the Princess's evil sister. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>



            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_CRUSADERS_HEADING_2</LocID>                     <Text>Grand Zieregal</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_CRUSADERS_TEXT_2</LocID>                        <Text>For centuries, Grand Zieregals, the highest in the hierarchy of the Children of the Source inquisitors, have been doing two things: they have controlled the believers' purity and hunted for Allmother's clones. \n\nNow, the last of them wishes to speak with Tin. His search for the legendary Lost Fleet is making waves, and his actions regarding the Princess are viewed as heresy by many. \n\nThe encounter could be dangerous, but Tin may also bring valuable information about the Lost Fleet. \n\nDespite her eagerness to join, the Princess was yet again left behind. She is too precious to stick her head into the beehive of the Grand Zieregal Fortress. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CAMPAIGN_CRUSADERS_LVL2_THE_END</LocID>                   <Text>The Princess and her sister are not the only beings capable of using more than a crumb of psionic powers. The Children of the Source starships had proven to be mighty psychers as well. \n\nThe Lost Fleet could become a force capable of shattering the dominance of the UNSS starships. Yet everyone claims that the entire Children of the Source fleet was destroyed centuries ago. Everyone except the Grand Zieregal. \n\nThat would be a poor excuse to justify a search in one of the most dangerous places in the Siren System. Poor indeed, if he was not the last guardian of the most secret knowledge of the church.   </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>


            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_CRUSADERS_HEADING_3</LocID>                     <Text>The Lost Fleet</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_CRUSADERS_TEXT_3</LocID>                        <Text>Something as gigantic as the massive starships of the Children of the Source shoudn't be easy to hide, but one could search through the uncharted wastelands of the Siren System for centuries and still find nothing. \n\nIn addition, there are areas just too dangerous to search. But, if you balance the risk with just a glimpse of hope, Tin is ready to take the chance. \n\nHe is adamant that one of the ancient battlefields, the unconquered target of the Children of the Source crusades, is hiding one of the ships of the Lost Fleet. \n\nFor a long time, the Tumori tribes have defended the place with unseen ferocity; let's hope their recent clashes with Fossorians have blunted their spears.  </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CAMPAIGN_CRUSADERS_LVL3_THE_END</LocID>                   <Text>The Lost Fleet was a myth. \n\nBut not entirely. \n\nThe Bright Star, the last of the original ships that brought the Children of the Source to the Siren System, survived the Grand Zieregals's purge. \n\nFurthermore, her connection to the Hesperidian-made ships of the UNSS fleet opens new, until now impossible, and highly unconventional ways to fight the UNSS forces that are now under the Princess's sister's control.  </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>


            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_CRUSADERS_HEADING_4</LocID>                     <Text>Swan Song</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>CUTSCENE_CAMPAIGN_CRUSADERS_TEXT_4</LocID>                        <Text>Once the Bright Star, the last starship of the Children of the Source, left the protective enclave of her shield, things were set in motion. But the Princess has a plan. \n\nHer army will attract the attention of the UNSS Fleet. And when the enemy gives the order to fire, the Princess will override their targeting by broadcasting the Litany from the Bright Star. \n\nIt will be a mortal gamble, but if the plan succeeds, her Sister and her forces will be swept away by a single magnificent blow of their own weapons. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CAMPAIGN_CRUSADERS_LVL4_THE_END</LocID>                   <Text>The Princess defeated her sister, but the price was high. With the final blast of psionic energy, a message was sent to the stars. \n\nThe Siren System proclaimed itself alive. \n\nThere is time and our heroes have earned a brief moment of rest. Friends and families will be reunited. With the help of the Princess, now the only being capable of enabling travel to distant stars, the Siren System will prosper again.  \n\nBut it's only a matter of time before someone or something else finds its way here. The "invitation" has been sent.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>


        </LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
