<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_TUTORIAL_01">

        <LanguageRef>LANG_EN</LanguageRef>

        <Contributors>
            <Name>Oxymoron Games</Name>
        </Contributors>

        <LocalizedStrings>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>NEXT_STEP</LocID>                                <Text>Next</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_PLAYER_NAME</LocID>                     <Text>Red Cadet</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_TUTORIAL_WELCOME</LocID>             <Text>Welcome to the tutorial!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_WELCOME</LocID>                      <Text><![CDATA[Hi, welcome to a tutorial that will teach you the basics of how to play Silence of the Siren!\nFirst, let's look at the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>controls</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_STEP_MOVE_CAMERA</LocID>             <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Move the camera</color> with the WASD/arrow keys, by moving the cursor to the edge of the screen or by holding the middle mouse button.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_STEP_ZOOM_CAMERA</LocID>             <Text><![CDATA[Great! Next, let's use the mouse wheel to <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>zoom the camera</color> in or out.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString><!--let's use the mouse wheel (or TODO buttons)-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_STEP_COMMANDERS</LocID>              <Text><![CDATA[Now, let's have a look at <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>commanders</color>, your active actors on the world/exploration map.\nYour only commander is selected. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Move him</color> by clicking the highlighted tile to plan a path, then click again to confirm the move!]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_STEP_DISCOVER</LocID>                <Text><![CDATA[Let's <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>head west</color> and find a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>container</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_CHEST</LocID>                        <Text><![CDATA[You found <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>a container</color>, open it, and <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>use the data fragment</color> inside. You will obtain some <color=SOTS_COLOR_XP>Experience points</color> - this will <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>level your commander up</color>!]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
           
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_ATTRIBUTES</LocID>                   <Text><![CDATA[Each commander has <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>three attributes</color>. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Exploration efficiency</color> increases your commander's speed by adding movement points and revealing more of the war fog around them. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Combat power</color> enhances the strength of the commander's army. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Ability strength</color> strengthens the commander's abilities, increases the overall amount, and replenishes their energy.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_SKILLS</LocID>                       <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Skills</color> - each commander can learn up to <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>8 skills</color>. Each skill has <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>three levels</color>. Commanders can <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>upgrade</color> skills from the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>first to second</color> level when they reach <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>level 5</color>, then from <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>second to third</color> level when they reach <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>level 10</color>. To learn <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>more info</color> about a skill, <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>hover over</color> it.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_LEVEL_UP</LocID>                     <Text><![CDATA[When commanders <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>level up</color>, you get to choose an <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>attribute</color> and a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>skill</color> to improve or learn. Do it now!]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_TURN_BASED_EXPLANATION</LocID>       <Text><![CDATA[Let's discuss the game's fundamental principles. It's <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>turn-based</color>, which means you have a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>limited number</color> of <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>actions per turn</color>. When a commander <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>uses all</color> of their <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>movement points</color>, you must <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>end the turn</color> to allow them to <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>replenish</color> their movement points. On this planet, each turn represents one phase of its rotation, and <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>four phases</color> make up <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>one cycle</color>. You can recruit new units at your base at the start of each cycle.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_RIGHT_PANEL_EXPLANATION</LocID>      <Text><![CDATA[On the right side of the screen, you can find the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>minimap</color>, a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>list of your bases</color>, <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>list of your commanders</color>, <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>buttons</color> for setting the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>animation speed</color> and a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>time panel with phase/cycle index</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_CHEST_HOARD</LocID>                  <Text><![CDATA[Let's pick up one more container. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Head north</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_END_TURN</LocID>                     <Text><![CDATA[If you run out of movement points, you must end your turn to replenish them. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Click</color> <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>End turn</color> in the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>bottom right corner</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_CHEST_HOARD_PART_TWO</LocID>         <Text><![CDATA[Move forward, and when you find and pick up the container, let's <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>hoard</color> its contents.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_OPEN_HERO_CARD</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[Now, you should have a new <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>consumable item</color> in your commander's inventory. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Open the commander card</color> by right-clicking the commander on the map or selecting them from the list on the right side of the screen.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_HERO_CARD_INFO</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[This <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>card</color> shows you all the essential information <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>about your commander</color>—their bio, level, attributes, acquired skills, items, and army details.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_HERO_CARD_UNDER_PORTRAIT</LocID>     <Text><![CDATA[Under the commander's portrait, you can find their <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>attributes</color>. They are:\n<color=SOTS_COLOR_XP>Experience points</color> displays the experience required to reach the next level. \n<color=SOTS_COLOR_MOVEMENT>Movement points</color> indicates the number of moves you can make per phase. (Depends on the terrain.)  \n<color=SOTS_COLOR_ENERGY>Energy points</color> are required to cast abilities and equip items and artifacts.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_HERO_CARD_MOVE_AND_ENERGY_POINTS</LocID><Text><![CDATA[After ending the turn, <color=SOTS_COLOR_MOVEMENT>Movement points</color> are completely replenished while some <color=SOTS_COLOR_ENERGY>Energy points</color> get restored depending on your commander's <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Ability strength</color> and equipment setup. You can check the replenished amount by hovering over the <color=SOTS_COLOR_ENERGY>Energy points</color> bar.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_HERO_CARD_MORALE</LocID>             <Text><![CDATA[This is <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Morale</color>. When the Morale number is <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>positive</color>, it represents a percentage chance of getting an <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>extra turn</color> in combat for each unit. If it's <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>negative</color>, it represents a percentage chance of <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>losing a turn</color> with each unit.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_HERO_CARD_ARMY</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[This card also <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>allows</color> you to <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>manage</color> the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>commander's army</color>. You can check your units' details or shuffle your army around. ]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_CONSUMABLE</LocID>                   <Text><![CDATA[But we're now interested in the item visible in the CONSUMABLES section. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Pick it up</color> and drop it <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>onto your commander's portrait</color> - or just <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>right click</color> on it.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_CLOSE_HERO_CARD</LocID>              <Text><![CDATA[Collecting these fragments lets you manage who gets that shiny experience and when. There are also a ton more consumable types!\nNow let's <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>close the card</color> and let's go <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>collect some more goodies!</color>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_ITEM_PICK_UP</LocID>                 <Text><![CDATA[Find and collect one item. Use the Alt key to highlight all interactive objects and pickups.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_INVENTORY_AGAIN</LocID>              <Text><![CDATA[Now <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>open your commander's card</color> with his inventory again!]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_ITEMS_AND_ENERGY</LocID>             <Text><![CDATA[Your commander has a few slots you can fill with valuable <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>items</color> that will help you on the map or in battles.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_ITEM_EQUIP</LocID>                   <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Equipping</color> most items will cost some amount of <color=SOTS_COLOR_ENERGY>energy points</color>. Lucky for you, this Datapad that increases Maj. Skaurov's XP income does not cost any! <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Equip</color> the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Datapad</color>!]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_CLOSE_HERO_CARD_RESOURCES</LocID>    <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Close</color> the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>commander's card</color> and <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>collect</color> some <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>resources</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_RESOURCES_EXPLANATION</LocID>        <Text><![CDATA[There are several resources in the game. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Aura Coins</color> serve as money. <color=SOTS_COLOR_LIMERITE>Limerite</color> and <color=SOTS_COLOR_ALLOYS>Alloy</color> are basic resources to build structures. <color=SOTS_COLOR_BIOMASS>Biomass</color> and <color=SOTS_COLOR_RADIANT>Radiant</color> are more unique resources needed for more advanced structures. <color=SOTS_COLOR_FUSION_CORE>Fusion Cores</color> are the most rare and valuable resource. You can activate special items on maps with them and buy any building for one fusion core.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_MINE_CAPTURE</LocID>                 <Text><![CDATA[Now <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>capture the Limerite Quarry</color> on the left.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_MINE_EXIT</LocID>                    <Text><![CDATA[Each mine <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>produces</color> a small amount of <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>resources per phase</color>. You can <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>upgrade the production</color> and the mine will generate more resources, or <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>build a defensive upgrade</color> to add turrets that will defend it against other players. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Close the upgrade dialog</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_MOVE_HERO_CLOSER_TO_BASE</LocID>     <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Move</color> your commander <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>closer to your base</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_HIGHLIGHT_EXPLAINED</LocID>          <Text><![CDATA[When exploring, you can check all the interactive objects around your commander. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Hold</color> the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Alt key</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
           
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_SELECT_BASE</LocID>                  <Text><![CDATA[Now check out your base, <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Trench Edge</color>. If the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>icons</color> next to the name are <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>green</color>, it means that you have <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>unused actions</color> there. You can <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>select your base</color> on the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>map</color> or in the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>list on the right</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_INTRODUCTION</LocID>                    <Text><![CDATA[This is your primary center of operations. Here, you can hire commanders and armies and build different upgrades. Let's have a look at the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>interface</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_LIST_AND_MINIMAP</LocID>                <Text><![CDATA[The <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>minimap</color> shows the location of this base on the world map.\nThe <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>list</color> below allows you to quickly switch between bases when you control more of them.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_BASE_DETAILS</LocID>                    <Text><![CDATA[The <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>details panel</color> gives you more insight into resource and unit production at the base.\nBelow it, the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>eight small buttons</color> give you quick access to the main functions that are otherwise opened by <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>clicking on individual buildings</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_BASE_GO_TO_BUILDING</LocID>             <Text><![CDATA[Now let's open the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>build & upgrade</color> catalog. Click the main building or the first shortcut button.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString><!--main building (TODO outline), shortcut button (TODO arrow) -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_BASE_BUILDING_CATALOG</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[This is where you expand your base. The buildings and upgrades can improve your economy and defenses, teach your commanders new abilities thanks to the academy, and allow you to recruit different units.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_BASE_BUILDING_CATALOG_ACADEMY</LocID>   <Text><![CDATA[Let's build the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Academy</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_BUILDING_EXPLANATION</LocID>            <Text><![CDATA[Each building can be bought for <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>aura coins and resources</color> or by spending one <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Fusion Core</color>. Be careful with the second option, though. Only a few Fusion Cores are available on each map.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_SWITCH_TO_ACADEMY</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[Now click the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Academy</color> building or the academy button to learn more about <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>commander abilities</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_IN_ACADEMY</LocID>                  <Text><![CDATA[Nice. We already have an info panel here. You can read the basics there, then click next.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_OUT_OFF_ACADEMY</LocID>             <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Leave</color> the academy by closing the window or clicking outside of it. Close the info window if it is still open.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_SWITCH_TO_RATLING_PROJECTS_V2</LocID>  <Text><![CDATA[Now <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>click</color> on the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Ratling Slum</color> building.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_IN_RATLING_PROJECTS</LocID>         <Text><![CDATA[You can see the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>hiring panel</color> for <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Ratlings</color>. Each unit comes in <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>two variants</color>: <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>basic</color> and <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>upgraded</color>. The <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>upgraded</color> units gain <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>better stats</color> and also a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>passive or active special ability</color>. The Ratlings become a ranged unit after getting upgraded. You can switch between both and choose which one to hire.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_OUT_OFF_RATLING_PROJECTS_V2</LocID>    <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Leave</color> the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Ratling Slum</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_IN_HIRING</LocID>                   <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Click</color> on the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Recruitment center building</color> or <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>the Hire units button</color> to learn more about hiring units.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_HIRING_INFO</LocID>                 <Text><![CDATA[Here, you can hire all available units thanks to your constructed buildings. The <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Hire all button</color> is available when you have enough resources for all units. If not, you can use the hire max buttons to buy as many available units as possible, starting from the lowest or highest tiers. You can switch between basic or upgraded units on each panel.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_HIRE_ALL</LocID>                    <Text><![CDATA[For now, just <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Hire all</color> the units.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_HIRE_ALL_CLOSE</LocID>              <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Close</color> the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Recruitment center</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_COMMANDERS</LocID>                  <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Click</color> on the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Hire commanders building</color> or the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Hire commanders button</color> to learn more about hiring commanders.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_HIRE_COMMANDERS_INFO</LocID>        <Text><![CDATA[You can hire a new commander here. There will always be a commander from the base's faction each cycle. You will also find any commanders who retreated from battle here. If you hire more than one commander per phase, the available armies will decrease in size.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_HIRE_COMMANDER</LocID>              <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Hire</color> a new commander.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_ARMY_INFO</LocID>                   <Text><![CDATA[Let's take a look at armies. The upper panel in a base's army UI shows your <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>garrisoned army</color>. If there's a siege, this army defends the base. The <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>army</color> in the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>lower panel</color> is just visiting and will leave when you return to the exploration map. You can move the armies or switch commanders with buttons on the right.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_UNIT_INFO</LocID>                   <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Right click</color> on a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>unit</color> to see its statistics.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_UNIT_SPLIT</LocID>                  <Text><![CDATA[If you have available army slots, you can fill them with your units. It may give you an advantage or more options during combat. Click "PICK" to <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Split the unit</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_UNIT_SPLIT_PLACE</LocID>            <Text><![CDATA[Place it in the empty slot, or cancel the selection.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_UNIT_UPGRADE</LocID>                <Text><![CDATA[Great! When you have upgraded barracks and hired basic units, you can upgrade them by clicking the gold button above the unit. (For a price, of course). Try to <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>upgrade any unit</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_ARMY_MERGE</LocID>                  <Text><![CDATA[Use the shortcut button to <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>move all garrisoned units</color> to the new commander.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BASE_EXIT_BASE</LocID>                   <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Return</color> to the exploration <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>map</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_HERO_MEETING</LocID>                     <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Move</color> your currently selected <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>commander</color> to <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>meet Major Skaurov, your original commander</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_HERO_MEETING_CARD</LocID>                <Text><![CDATA[This is the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>commander's meeting card</color>. Here you can <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>exchange items</color> and <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>trade armies</color> (Trading armies will cost you some <color=SOTS_COLOR_MOVEMENT>movement points</color>)]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_HERO_MEETING_CARD_MOVE_ARMY</LocID>      <Text><![CDATA[All commanders have to have at least one unit. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Move</color> all the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>units to</color> your <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>stronger commander</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_HERO_MEETING_CARD_CLOSE</LocID>          <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Close</color> the meeting <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>card</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_HERO_WEAK_ARMY_INFO</LocID>              <Text><![CDATA[It's time to start taking over some guarded structures. When you <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>attack neutral armies</color> (these are just units with <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>no commander</color>) and you are much <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>stronger</color>, sometimes you will get the option to let them <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>join</color> or let them <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>run</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_GO_TO_COMBAT</LocID>                     <Text><![CDATA[If you <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>hover over</color> the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>enemies on the left</color>, a tooltip gives you an indication of <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>how dangerous</color> it's going to be. We changed your army a bit for this tutorial. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Let's battle!</color>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_LAYOUT</LocID>              <Text><![CDATA[This is what a simple battlefield looks like. Attacking armies always start on the left side and have a slight advantage thanks to a higher initiative. Each unit has its own initiative that determines its order. You can see the order of the units at the bottom of the screen.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_UNIT_OPEN_CARD</LocID>      <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Right click</color> on the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>unit card</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_UNIT_INFO</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[Here, you can check the details (like stats and special abilities) of any unit on the battlefield. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Close the unit card</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_UNIT_RANGE</LocID>          <Text><![CDATA[You can see the movement range of any unit when you <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>hover over them while holding Shift</color>. Let's <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>try it now</color>!]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_BASIC_INFO</LocID>          <Text><![CDATA[Each unit has a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>range of possible actions</color> they can do during their turn:\n<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Move \nMove and attack\nShoot if a target is within their range \nLimited-range units move and shoot</color>, but we don't have any.)]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_WAIT</LocID>                <Text><![CDATA[Units can also <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>choose to wait</color>, indicated by a yellow <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>button</color> with a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>clock</color> icon above the active unit. This action <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>moves</color> the unit to the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>end</color> of the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>current round's order</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_SKIP</LocID>                <Text><![CDATA[Units can also <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>choose to pass</color> their <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>turn</color>, represented by a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>button</color> located to the right of the 'wait' button.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_LOG_INFO</LocID>            <Text><![CDATA[You can see the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>combat log</color> on the right. It logs every move that happens in the combat.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_AUTO_BATTLE_BUTTON</LocID>  <Text><![CDATA[Above the log, there are some control buttons. The first is <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Auto combat</color>, which allows you to let the computer quickly finish the battle.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_RETREAT_BUTTON</LocID>      <Text><![CDATA[The second one is <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Retreat</color>. If you anticipate defeat but don't want to lose your commander, you can sacrifice your army and let your commander retreat to a base to re-hire some new mercs.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_SURRENDER_BUTTON</LocID>    <Text><![CDATA[The next button is to <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Surrender</color>. You can pay a price to leave the battle without losses.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_SPEED_BUTTONS</LocID>       <Text><![CDATA[The buttons in the next section allow you to adjust the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>speed of the animations and movement</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_HEXES</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[With the last button, you can toggle the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Hex grid</color><color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>on or off</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_RANGED_UNIT_SELECT</LocID>  <Text><![CDATA[Sometimes, it is better to let the enemy come to you, especially if you have a ranged unit and the enemy doesn't. Let's <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>pass</color> this turn with our <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>meelee units</color> to <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>select</color> our <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>shooter</color> unit.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString><!-- Wait for the enemy to come into the range.--> <!--Wait with “Ratling gunner”.-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_RANGED_UNIT_SHOOT</LocID>   <Text><![CDATA[Each shooter has a range where they shoot more precisely and inflict more damage. The <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Red outline</color> shows you where their <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>precise range</color> ends. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Shoot an enemy unit</color> even though they're still out of range.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString><!-- Wait for the enemy to come into the range.--> <!--Wait with “Ratling gunner”.-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_HEX_ATTACKS</LocID>         <Text><![CDATA[The battlefield layout and controls are based on hexes, so when you aim your <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>attack</color>, aim at the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>hexes</color>, <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>not at a unit</color> itself. If the situation becomes confusing, use the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>CTRL key</color> to <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>shrink all units</color> to see the situation better. Each unit also has a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>counter attack</color> it can use when it gets <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>attacked</color> the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>first time</color> during a round. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Now move your melee units</color> closer so they can attack.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_RANGE_UNIT_AGAIN</LocID>    <Text><![CDATA[It is your ranged unit's turn again. Use it to thin the enemy unit's stack some more. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Attack</color> with your <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Ranged unit</color> again.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString><!--Try some melee attack. Aim on the border of hex under enemy units. -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_MELEE_UNIT</LocID>          <Text><![CDATA[You can <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>attack</color> the enemy <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>from any direction</color>, aiming at the hex's edge from the direction you want to attack. The direction has no effect on the inflicted damage. Now use your <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Melee unit to attack</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString><!--Try some melee attack. Aim on the border of hex under enemy units. -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_WIN</LocID>                 <Text><![CDATA[You should know the basics now, so put them to good use and <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Win</color> the battle.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_FIRST_BATTLE_WON</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[Congratulations, <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>you won</color> your first battle! <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Click close</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_LEARN_SKILL_TECHIE</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[With the XP from the battle, you leveled up your commander again. Now <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>choose Techie</color>. It's a skill that allows you to use commander abilities. \nDon't forget to choose an attribute too.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_LEARN_ABILITY</LocID>                    <Text><![CDATA[Abilities have three skill levels. With each level, abilities become stronger. Every time you learn or improve an ability skill, you can choose a new ability. For now <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>learn Long-range artillery</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_VISIT_DOJO</LocID>                       <Text><![CDATA[Back on the map, the structure in front of you is a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Swordsman's Sanctuary</color>. Like many other structures on the map, the Swordsman's Sanctuary gives you a reward when you visit it. You can see info about the structure if you hover over it before you enter. Now <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>go check it out!</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_LEARN_SKILL_CHESS_MASTER</LocID>         <Text><![CDATA[Chessmaster is a skill that allows you to position all your units freely in an area on your side of the battlefield before combat starts. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Learn the skill</color>. \nDon't forget to choose an attribute too.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_LEARN_SKILL_GLOBETROTTER</LocID>         <Text><![CDATA[The <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Globetrotter</color> skill unlocks the option to learn various exploration abilities. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Learn the skill</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_LEARN_ABILITY_RUSH</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Learn Rush</color>, a useful ability that allows you to restore a bit of movement each turn.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_USE_EXPLORATION_ABILITY</LocID>          <Text><![CDATA[There are two main categories of commander abilities: the ones used in combat and the abilities used on the exploration map. \nThe <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Globetrotter skill</color> allows you to use <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>abilities</color> on the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>map</color>. You can use only one ability per turn. You can open abilities from the commander card, but let's try a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>shortcut</color> from the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>commander action menu</color> on the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>right panel</color>, or <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>left click</color> on your <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>commander</color>. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Open</color> the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>ability book</color> and <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>use Rush</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BUILDING_INFO</LocID>                    <Text><![CDATA[Each commander can <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>build</color> various <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>structures</color> on the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>exploration map</color>. They can be defensive or offensive, but we'll try a resource-gathering structure.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_MOVE_TO_BUILD</LocID>                    <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Let's move</color> to a more <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>convenient location</color> to try that.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_LEARN_PROBE_INFO</LocID>                 <Text><![CDATA[We will build a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>mining probe</color>. It will <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>gather resources</color> for you. Which <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>resource</color> will depend on the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>terrain</color>. The <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>longer</color> you keep the probe <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>active</color>, the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>more resources</color> it will collect. You can <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>dismantle</color> the probe <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>whenever you want</color>, but <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>so can your enemies!</color>. It becomes active once the activation time passes or when an activation upgrade is added.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BUILD_PROBE</LocID>                      <Text><![CDATA[Use the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>left mouse button</color> on your <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>commander</color> to <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>open</color> a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>commander action menu</color> again and <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>build</color> a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>mining probe</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_BUILDER_SKILL</LocID>                    <Text><![CDATA[Once you learn the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Builder skill</color>, you will be able to <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>build more <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>advanced versions</color> of the <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>structures</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
           
            <!-- Do we call it a book officially? :) -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_LAST_COMBAT</LocID>                      <Text><![CDATA[Now, let's battle some more and try to use a unit special and a commander's ability in combat. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Attack the enemy</color> to the northwest!]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_START_COMBAT_TACTICS</LocID>             <Text><![CDATA[Your commander's Chessmaster skill lets you position your units before the start of the combat. When you are ready, <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>click the end tactics button.</color>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_USE_UNIT_SPECIAL_ABILITY</LocID>         <Text><![CDATA[When units get <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>upgraded</color>, they gain a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>special ability</color>. Try to use one of your unit's special abilities by <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>clicking the button</color> and <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>choosing a target</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_USE_COMBAT_ABILITY</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[Let's try a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>commander combat ability</color> next. You can only use one commander ability each round. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Click</color> on your <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>commander's portrait</color> and select <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Long range artillery</color>. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Use it</color> on a <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>group of enemy units</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_LAST_BATTLE_WON</LocID>                  <Text><![CDATA[Congratulations, <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>you won</color> your second battle. <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Click close</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>TUTORIAL_01_TUTORIAL_COMPLETED</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[Congratulations, you have <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>completed the tutorial</color>. Ready for the real thing? <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Click Next</color> to <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>return</color> to <color=SOTS_COLOR_GOLD>Main menu</color>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

        </LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
