<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_HIVEMIND">

        <LanguageRef>LANG_EN</LanguageRef>

        <Contributors>
            <Name>Oxymoron Games</Name>
        </Contributors>

        <LocalizedStrings>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>FACTION_HIVEMIND</LocID>                                             <Text>Tumori Tribes</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
                                                                                                                        
            <!--Unit names-->                                                                                           
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_SWARM</LocID>                                          <Text>Fungor</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_SWARM_UPG</LocID>                                      <Text>Ripe Fungor</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <!--            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_BEHOLDER</LocID>                                       <Text>Askon</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_BEHOLDER_UPG</LocID>                                   <Text>Mature Askon</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_METAMORPH</LocID>                                      <Text>Metamorph</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_METAMORPH_UPG</LocID>                                  <Text>Metamorph Wielder</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <!--            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_CLAW</LocID>                                           <Text>Slugtor</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_CLAW_UPG</LocID>                                       <Text>Slugtor Brute</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <!--            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_ASSSHOOTER</LocID>                                     <Text>Malarion Nymph</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_ASSSHOOTER_UPG</LocID>                                 <Text>Malarion Imago</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_PREDATOR</LocID>                                       <Text>Skull Collector</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_PREDATOR_UPG</LocID>                                   <Text>Skull Hunter</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <!--            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_DRAGON</LocID>                                         <Text>Raughir</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_DRAGON_UPG</LocID>                                     <Text>Ancient Raughir</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_WAR_MACHINE_GLUE_GRENADE_LAUNCHER</LocID>              <Text>Goo Spitter</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <!--Unit abilities-->
            
            <!-- TODO texts from 2025/07 -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_METAMORPH_SPECIAL_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                  <Text>Each turn randomly transforms into another unit on the battlefield.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_METAMORPH_UPG_SPECIAL_DESCRIPTION</LocID>              <Text>Transforms into any chosen unit on the battlefield.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>STACK_STATUS_EFFECT_METAMORPH</LocID>                                <Text>Morphed</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>STACK_STATUS_EFFECT_METAMORPH_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                    <Text>The unit has transformed into another unit.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <!--the rest-->

            <!--Unit description-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_SWARM_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                              <Text>In combat, the swarm host individuals are responsible for all the heavy lifting, while the flying fungi clusters offer at least some level of protection. As the elders say, "Better have your pants full of holes than expose your ... never mind". </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_SWARM_UPG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                          <Text>"Ripe" means that there is barely any space left in the Fungor, and the swarm is nearly ready to "resettle" to a new, more demanding host. But, why not take the old host for one final, hell of a ride! </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_BEHOLDER_UPG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                       <Text>In a tribal society where being a brave warrior is the norm, will I be considered "less alpha" if I choose a host that avoids melee? Yes, you definitely will, my friend. But at the same time, you will most likely see all those who mocked you die in most gruesome ways. </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_METAMORPH_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                          <Text>Claws are priceless in melee, but have you ever watched a girl with a nail job trying to pick up a coin? Therefore, becoming a Metamorph is a compromise; you can fight if necessary, but you can also wipe your bum without an unwanted surgery. </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_METAMORPH_UPG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                      <Text>They can turn into almost anything. Natural-born spies, you think? Maybe, but only to the moment they open their mouths. See, the Tumori "speech" is reserved only for the simplest communication, like "watch out" and "human with axe", and "behind you". Still, a great camouflage! </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_CLAW_UPG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                           <Text>A lifetime of boxing puts your mind "at ease" (by severely damaging your brain), and the same happens if the swarm merges with the Slugtor for too long. To put it mildly, they excel in "the ring", just don't expect any in-depth conversations. </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_ASSSHOOTER_UPG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                     <Text>Inside the Primals technology, you find harmless crystals and the strange, luminous, caustic goo. We believe the goo serves as energy storage. But why do I mention it? Because these creatures absorb it like a sponge. </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_PREDATOR_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                           <Text>There is a rumor about the first wave of human settlers that arrived in the Siren System. Those were turbulent times, and many small settlements in the deep jungles and border regions went silent without anyone noticing. All the settlers died ... or not? </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_PREDATOR_UPG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                       <Text>We humans tend to blame the Uncanny Valley principle, but let's face it. We all imagined our first encounter with humanoid aliens a lot more like one of the "special adventures" of Captain Kirk. That's why we hate the Skull Hunters so much. </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_DRAGON_UPG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                         <Text>For the full control over Raughir's powers, the swarm has to undergo so many physiological changes that when the Raughir is defeated, the swarm cannot leave the dying host's body anymore. Unlike other hosts, merging with a Raughir is a one-way ticket. That's why they fight so hard. </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_WAR_MACHINE_GLUE_GRENADE_LAUNCHER_DESCRIPTION</LocID>  <Text>Even today, most fights are decided by melee, the speed of movement is crucial, and a few extra inches of distance can mean the difference between life and death. Therefore, even the strongest foes are half as dangerous with their legs glued to the ground.   </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <!--Unit description (ALREADY in Patches - in this doc. only for info) -->
<!--
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_BEHOLDER_DESCRIPTION</LocID>              <Text>Once they are blessed by the Primal's blast stone and inhabited by the swarm, the Askons begin to form their tumors. The perfect host for any hunter-warrior who does not prefer the way of claws and teeth.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_CLAW_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                  <Text>Brutal monsters, perfected by the parasitic swarm. It is said that the mind of the beast can't be completely subdued. It slowly blends with the swarm's consciousness, which becomes addicted to the most gory ways of fighting.     </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_ASSSHOOTER_DESCRIPTION</LocID>            <Text>The tribes from swamp territories are using the flying hosts to collect the treasures of starship wreckages hidden behind the impenetrable fog and murky waters. Even implanting parts of machines into their own bodies.      </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_DRAGON_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                <Text>The time of the Raughirs is almost over. The ancient genetic matrices are wearing off and most offspring are being born deformed or untamable. However, each successful attempt will overshadow dozens of previous failures.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
-->

            <!--Unit abilities-->


            <!--Hero names-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_1</LocID>     <Text>Sage Requan-Cher</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_2</LocID>     <Text>Voliantros</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_3</LocID>     <Text>Voice of Tumori</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_4</LocID>     <Text>Man-eater </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_5</LocID>     <Text>Root</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_6</LocID>     <Text>Santarsí</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_7</LocID>     <Text>Crimson Malice</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_8</LocID>     <Text>The Undying</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_9</LocID>     <Text>Spore</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_10</LocID>    <Text>Carnivora</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_11</LocID>    <Text>Harbringer </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_12</LocID>    <Text>Fol the Primal </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_13</LocID>    <Text>The Bugsmasher</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            

            <!--Hero description-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_1_DESCRIPTION</LocID>              <Text>As a young warrior swarm, it went on many adventures with its friend Voliantros. However, many cycles have passed since, and now its most powerful weapon is the knowledge of some of the most hidden secrets of the Siren System.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_2_DESCRIPTION</LocID>              <Text>Voliantros accompanied Requan-cher on many adventures of their youth. While Requan stayed open-minded to cooperation with the Outworlders, Voliantros chose the path slippery with violet and red blood. The path of war against all Outworlders.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_3_DESCRIPTION</LocID>              <Text>The voice of Tumori must become the bridge between humans and tribesmen. If it fails, the world as Tumori know it, will burn. Not now, not in a decade, but leaf after leaf, tree after tree. There are simply too many humans.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_4_DESCRIPTION</LocID>              <Text>A brutal monster that decided to walk the path of gore. It does not remember anything from before entering its Slugtor host. It only knows there was something worth forgetting. Life is easy now, and in the middle of the fight, Carnivora is happy again.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_5_DESCRIPTION</LocID>              <Text>Once there were forests of trees that formed crystals within their wood. But when the Children of the Source came, they burned them all. Miracously, a single seedling was found. The Root bound its life to its protection because it's much more than just a tree. It's a symbol of hope.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_6_DESCRIPTION</LocID>              <Text>Tumori made their home on broken worlds, but their ancestors handed down many gifts to help their heirs. Santarsí became a guardian of one of them and merged the consciousness of its swarm with a sentient artifact.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_7_DESCRIPTION</LocID>              <Text>Growing crystals are a slow, but terminal illness that will consume all inherited worlds. But Crimson Malice and its disciples believe that the crystals are forming a global supermachine. If you listen closely, the whispers of the final gift of Primals can already be heard.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_8_DESCRIPTION</LocID>              <Text>For a thousand years he has walked under the stars. But such a long life is highly unnatural, even for the longaevous Tumori swarms. Most beings think time is like a river that flows swiftly in one direction. For the Undying, time is an ocean in a storm. A storm that settles only in the fight to the death.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_9_DESCRIPTION</LocID>              <Text>The more individuals a hive has, the more intellectual power it vields. Spore is a superhive, a rarity; its swarm is several times larger than the usual count. If the number grows even more, it will end up only speaking in mathematical formulas.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_10_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Its name was Sadu, and it lived a life of peace, surrounded by trees and its tribe. In one short year, the human settlers made the forest and the whole tribe history. That's why Sadu took a war-name and became the monster that the humans saw in it from the very beginning.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_11_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Tumori idealists believe that coexistence with humans is possible, but even the most naive ones do not believe in peace with the Fossorians. The Harbringer was made for a sole purpose. To inflict fear. That's the only currency the wicked mole race understands.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_12_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Fol devoted the life of its swarm to the study of ancient Primals. It is said that through the many eyes of its artificial face, it can see remains of the Psychosphere, an information field that connects and surrounds every Primal creation.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>HERO_HIVEMIND_13_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Children of the Source never learned the fate of their last crusade. Only a whisper came back to Temple City. Uncertain words about a mysterious tribesman who kept luring the Children's generals deeper and deeper into the swamps of Chimera.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_SWARM_UPG_INFO_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                     <Text>When hit, the remaining units split in half. Melee attack inflicts poison damage.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_BEHOLDER_UPG_INFO_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                  <Text>Has a ranged attack. When shooting an enemy, a there's a 20% chance to hit other enemies with a secondady beam.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ABILITY_UNIT_HIVEMIND_CLAW_UPG_SPECIAL</LocID>                       <Text>Activates a cellular armor which provides resistance to minor damage.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>STACK_STATUS_EFFECT_CLAW_SHIELD</LocID>                              <Text>Scratch resistance</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>STACK_STATUS_EFFECT_CLAW_SHIELD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                  <Text>Incoming damage below 20% of total health is reduced to 1.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ABILITY_UNIT_HIVEMIND_PREDATOR_UPG_SPECIAL</LocID>                   <Text>Hit any enemy on the battlefield and returns. Target cannot retaliate.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>ABILITY_UNIT_HIVEMIND_ASSSHOOTER_UPG_SPECIAL</LocID>                 <Text>Energy projectile, hits multiple enemies and deals shock damage to TECH units.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_DRAGON_UPG_PASSIVE_INFO_DESCRIPTION</LocID>            <Text>Can jump over obstacles. Can move and shoot with limited range causing poison damage. </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_UNIT_HIVEMIND_CLAW_UPG_PASSIVE_INFO_DESCRIPTION</LocID>         <Text>Can attack up to 3 enemies standing next to each other and deals bleeding damage. </Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_ASSSHOOTER_PASSIVE_INFO_DESCRIPTION</LocID>            <Text>Has a ranged attack. Can jump over obstacles.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>UNIT_HIVEMIND_WAR_MACHINE_GLUE_GRENADE_LAUNCHER_INFO_DESCRIPTION</LocID> <Text>Once each turn, a sticky Glue Grenade is unleashed, striking multiple enemies and bogging them down.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_EFFECT_SPLIT_ITSELF</LocID>                                  <Text>{CombatActor} has split.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <!--Notes-->
<!--
            1) Skull-hunters cult has spread amongs the most feral tribes.
            2) Only extremely strong and disciplined swarms can tame such a powerful hosts.
            3)Human homeworld must be a horrible place if it give a birth to such a predatory species.
-->
        
        </LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
